0	R.H.	B-ORG
1	Saunders	I-ORG
2	(	O
3	St.	B-ORG
4	Lawrence	I-ORG
5	River	I-ORG
6	)	O
7	(	O
8	968	O
9	MW	O
10	)	O

0	;	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	Anders	B-PER
4	Lindström	I-PER
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	Karl	B-PER
1	Ove	I-PER
2	Knausgård	I-PER
3	(	O
4	born	O
5	1968	O
6	)	O

0	Atlantic	B-LOC
1	City	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	New	I-LOC
4	Jersey	I-LOC

0	Her	O
1	daughter	O
2	from	O
3	the	O
4	second	O
5	marriage	O
6	was	O
7	Marie	B-PER
8	d'Agoult	I-PER
9	(	O
10	1805–1876	O
11	)	O
12	,	O
13	who	O
14	in	O
15	turn	O
16	gave	O
17	birth	O
18	to	O
19	several	O
20	children	O
21	,	O
22	among	O
23	them—from	O
24	her	O
25	liaison	O
26	to	O
27	Franz	B-PER
28	Liszt	I-PER
29	–-	O
30	Cosima	B-PER
31	Wagner	I-PER
32	(	O
33	1837–1930	O
34	)	O
35	.	O

0	St.	B-ORG
1	Mary	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	Catholic	I-ORG
4	Church	I-ORG
5	(	I-ORG
6	Sandusky	I-ORG
7	,	I-ORG
8	Ohio	I-ORG
9	)	I-ORG

0	Shhh	B-ORG
1	...	I-ORG
2	Do	I-ORG
3	n't	I-ORG
4	Tell	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Antonín	B-PER
1	Rýgr	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1970–72	O
4	)	O

0	Dia	B-PER
1	Evtimova	I-PER
2	Catalina	B-PER
3	Castaño	I-PER
4	Dinah	B-PER
5	Pfizenmaier	I-PER
6	Tatjana	B-PER
7	Malek	I-PER

0	102.7	O
1	MHz	O
2	Triple	B-ORG
3	J	I-ORG
4	–	O
5	ABC	B-ORG

0	*20px	O
1	Idaho	B-ORG
2	State	I-ORG
3	Highway	I-ORG
4	5	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Atelocentra	B-LOC
2	''	O
3	Meyrick	O
4	,	O
5	1884	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Antarctic	B-LOC
3	prion	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	James	B-PER
1	Franco	I-PER
2	(	O
3	M.F.A	O
4	.	O

0	Civic	B-ORG
1	Freedom	I-ORG
2	Party	I-ORG

0	キイロキリガ	O
1	—	O
2	Xanthia	B-LOC
3	togata	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	(	O
6	Esper	O
7	,	O
8	1788	O
9	)	O

0	*August	O
1	8	O
2	–	O
3	Craig	B-PER
4	Breslow	I-PER

0	He	O
1	has	O
2	also	O
3	won	O
4	the	O
5	Japan	B-ORG
6	Senior	I-ORG
7	Open	I-ORG
8	twice	O
9	.	O

0	His	O
1	great-grandson	O
2	is	O
3	director	O
4	Whit	B-PER
5	Stillman	I-PER
6	.	O

0	''	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	Chauliodus	B-ORG
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	''	O

0	Janaki]]	O
1	,	O
2	S.	B-PER
3	P.	I-PER
4	Balasubrahmanyam	I-PER

0	:	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	Thornhill	B-ORG
4	Islanders	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	defeated	O
8	Markham	B-ORG
9	Waxers	I-ORG
10	''4-games-to-3	O
11	''	O

0	Obituary	O
1	of	O
2	Juliette	B-PER
3	Peirce	I-PER
4	.	O

0	78	O
1	''	O
2	in	O
3	Osnabrück	B-LOC
4	.	O

0	Gian	B-PER
1	Girolamo	I-PER
2	Albani	I-PER

0	``	O
1	Rhinestone	B-ORG
2	Cowboy	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Larry	B-PER
6	Weiss	I-PER
7	)	O
8	-	O
9	3:15	O

0	*Episode	O
1	9	O
2	-	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Conlan	I-PER

0	Antawn	B-PER
1	Jamison	I-PER
2	(	O
3	28	O
4	)	O

0	1978	O
1	demo	O
2	released	O
3	on	O
4	Off	B-ORG
5	the	I-ORG
6	Wall	I-ORG
7	(	I-ORG
8	Special	I-ORG
9	Edition	I-ORG
10	)	I-ORG
11	''	O
12	(	O
13	2001	O
14	)	O

0	Eveno-Bytantaysky	B-LOC
1	National	I-LOC
2	District	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Euxoa	B-ORG
2	centralis	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Staudinger	O
6	,	O
7	1889	O
8	)	O

0	Diocese	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	San	I-LOC
3	Andrés	I-LOC
4	Tuxtla	I-LOC

0	Palisades	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	New	I-LOC
3	York	I-LOC

0	Rosephanye	B-PER
1	Powell	I-PER
2	(	O
3	born	O
4	1962	O
5	)	O

0	Chum	B-LOC
1	Ta	I-LOC
2	Bong	I-LOC
3	District	I-LOC

0	Epica	B-ORG
1	–	O
2	Consign	B-ORG
3	to	I-ORG
4	Oblivion	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	''	O
1	Epirrhoe	B-LOC
2	rivata	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Hübner	O
6	,	O
7	1813	O
8	)	O

0	**	O
1	''	O
2	Justice	B-ORG
3	League	I-ORG
4	Elite	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	:	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	found	O
3	in	O
4	Peru	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	**	O
1	Ecuador	B-LOC
2	:	O
3	7	O
4	%	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	population	O

0	Translator	O
1	of	O
2	KCCV-FM	B-ORG
3	,	O
4	Overland	B-LOC
5	Park	I-LOC
6	,	I-LOC
7	Kansas	I-LOC

0	Mrs	O
1	Brigitte	B-PER
2	Vallée	I-PER
3	.	O

0	Lipiny	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Ciechanów	I-LOC
3	County	I-LOC

0	Tatiana	B-PER
1	Volosozhar	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Maxim	B-PER
4	Trankov	I-PER

0	Raymerville	B-LOC
1	–	I-LOC
2	Markville	I-LOC
3	East	I-LOC
4	,	I-LOC
5	Ontario	I-LOC

0	Robert	B-PER
1	Maxwell	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	5th	I-PER
4	Lord	I-PER
5	Maxwell	I-PER
6	(	O
7	1493–1546	O
8	)	O

0	Prince	B-PER
1	Rupert	I-PER
2	of	I-PER
3	the	I-PER
4	Rhine	I-PER
5	15	O
6	August	O
7	1672	O
8	–	O
9	19	O
10	November	O
11	1682	O

0	Železničná	B-ORG
1	spoločnosť	I-ORG
2	Slovensko	I-ORG

0	On	O
1	February	O
2	6	O
3	,	O
4	1925	O
5	he	O
6	retired	O
7	from	O
8	active	O
9	duty	O
10	and	O
11	died	O
12	in	O
13	Santiago	B-LOC
14	in	O
15	1938	O
16	.	O

0	The	O
1	67	O
2	's	O
3	finished	O
4	in	O
5	last	O
6	place	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	2012–13	B-ORG
10	OHL	I-ORG
11	season	I-ORG
12	with	O
13	just	O
14	16	O
15	wins	O
16	.	O

0	Internet	B-ORG
1	Exchange	I-ORG
2	Point	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	IXP	O
5	)	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	released	O
3	as	O
4	the	O
5	first	O
6	single	O
7	from	O
8	their	O
9	2004	O
10	album	O
11	Everybody	B-ORG
12	Loves	I-ORG
13	a	I-ORG
14	Happy	I-ORG
15	Ending	I-ORG
16	''	O
17	and	O
18	is	O
19	the	O
20	first	O
21	single	O
22	that	O
23	features	O
24	both	O
25	original	O
26	members	O
27	Roland	B-PER
28	Orzabal	I-PER
29	and	O
30	Curt	B-PER
31	Smith	I-PER
32	since	O
33	1990	O
34	.	O

0	Conservative]]	O
1	Leader	O
2	David	B-PER
3	Cameron	I-PER
4	)	O

0	Much	O
1	of	O
2	the	O
3	story	O
4	takes	O
5	place	O
6	in	O
7	Flagstaff	B-LOC
8	,	I-LOC
9	Arizona	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	where	O
12	Sgt	O
13	.	O

0	''	O
1	Invisible	B-ORG
2	Touch	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	–	O
5	Genesis	B-ORG

0	United	B-PER
1	States	I-PER
2	Senate	I-PER
3	Librarian	I-PER

0	Live	B-ORG
1	at	I-ORG
2	Sin-é	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	Legacy	I-ORG
5	Edition	I-ORG
6	)	I-ORG
7	''	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Calgary	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O
5	,	O
6	'	O
7	''	O
8	Canada	B-LOC
9	''	O
10	'	O

0	*2001	O
1	–	O
2	Hugh	B-PER
3	Hefner	I-PER
4	,	O
5	Roastmaster	O
6	Jimmy	B-PER
7	Kimmel	I-PER

0	Aigle	B-ORG
1	Noir	I-ORG
2	AC	I-ORG

0	Hathaways	B-LOC
1	Mountain	I-LOC
2	Pines	I-LOC
3	,	I-LOC
4	California	I-LOC

0	Peter	B-PER
1	T.	I-PER
2	King	I-PER

0	Charlie	B-PER
1	Clouser	I-PER
2	–	O
3	Nine	B-ORG
4	Inch	I-ORG
5	Nails	I-ORG

0	Former	B-ORG
1	collegiate	I-ORG
2	church	I-ORG
3	St	I-ORG
4	Bartholomew	I-ORG
5	,	O
6	Liège	B-LOC

0	Zlaté	B-LOC
1	Moravce	I-LOC
2	District	I-LOC

0	Wilhelm	B-PER
1	Gustav	I-PER
2	Franz	I-PER
3	Herter	I-PER

0	Thomasville	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Missouri	I-LOC

0	Clement	B-ORG
1	Poitrenaud	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	14	O
4	.	O

0	Yahn	B-LOC
1	|	O
2	Yazdan	B-LOC
3	Chah	I-LOC
4	|	O
5	Yegi	B-LOC
6	|	O
7	Yekkeh	B-LOC
8	Derakht	I-LOC
9	|	O
10	Yosht	B-LOC
11	|	O
12	Yusefabad	B-LOC
13	|	O
14	Yush	B-LOC
15	|	O
16	Yushu	B-LOC

0	1982	B-ORG
1	Tour	I-ORG
2	de	I-ORG
3	France	I-ORG

0	John	B-PER
1	Denison-Pender	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	1st	I-PER
4	Baron	I-PER
5	Pender	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Glyphipterix	B-LOC
2	iometalla	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Meyrick	O
6	,	O
7	1880	O
8	)	O

0	''	O
1	Zygaena	B-LOC
2	cynarae	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Esper	O
6	,	O
7	1789	O
8	)	O

0	''	O
1	Super	B-ORG
2	World	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Sports	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	Chananel	B-PER
1	ben	I-PER
2	Chushiel	I-PER

0	Bobby	B-PER
1	Rush	I-PER
2	(	O
3	D	O
4	)	O

0	Legend	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Chun	I-ORG
3	Hyang	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	BBC	B-ORG
1	(	O
2	Test	B-ORG
3	Match	I-ORG
4	Special	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	)	O

0	Bruce	B-PER
1	Beresford	I-PER
2	(	O
3	Non-Jew	O
4	)	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	also	O
3	released	O
4	along	O
5	with	O
6	Visual	B-ORG
7	Studio	I-ORG
8	2005	I-ORG
9	,	O
10	Microsoft	B-ORG
11	SQL	I-ORG
12	Server	I-ORG
13	2005	I-ORG
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	BizTalk	B-ORG
17	2006	O
18	.	O

0	Leonardo	B-PER
1	Rodríguez	I-PER
2	Solís	I-PER

0	She	O
1	was	O
2	born	O
3	in	O
4	Aldsworth	B-LOC
5	,	O
6	Gloucestershire	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	England	B-LOC
9	on	O
10	10	O
11	January	O
12	1836	O
13	.	O

0	**	O
1	Kyoto	B-ORG
2	National	I-ORG
3	Museum	I-ORG
4	(	O
5	early	O
6	production	O
7	cast	O
8	)	O

0	List	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	years	I-ORG
3	in	I-ORG
4	Brazil	I-ORG

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	found	O
3	in	O
4	Mexico	B-LOC
5	,	O
6	Guatemala	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	Costa	B-LOC
9	Rica	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	Panama	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Colombia	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	Venezuela	B-LOC
16	and	O
17	Brazil	B-LOC
18	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Michele	B-PER
3	Morosini	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	(	O
7	1308–1382	O
8	)	O
9	was	O
10	''doge	O
11	''	O
12	from	O
13	June	O
14	1382	O
15	until	O
16	his	O
17	death	O
18	in	O
19	October	O
20	of	O
21	the	O
22	same	O
23	year	O
24	.	O

0	20px	O
1	Władysław	B-PER
2	I	I-PER
3	the	I-PER
4	Elbow-high	I-PER

0	Misawa	B-ORG
1	AB	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	Japan	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	29	O
6	November	O
7	1965	O
8	–	O
9	15	O
10	May	O
11	1971	O

0	Flatnose	B-LOC
1	xenocongrid	I-LOC
2	eel	I-LOC

0	He	O
1	resigned	O
2	in	O
3	March	O
4	1906	O
5	to	O
6	run	O
7	for	O
8	West	B-LOC
9	Hobart	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	but	O
12	was	O
13	unsuccessful	O
14	.	O

0	Lăpugiu	B-LOC
1	de	I-LOC
2	Jos	I-LOC

0	Chinantec	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	Ozumacín	I-LOC

0	*October	O
1	4	O
2	–	O
3	Drew	B-PER
4	Stubbs	I-PER

0	16th	B-ORG
1	Troop	I-ORG
2	Carrier	I-ORG
3	Squadron	I-ORG
4	:	O
5	attached	O
6	14	O
7	November	O
8	1954	O
9	–	O
10	8	O
11	July	O
12	1955	O

0	File	O
1	:	O
2	Bdg	O
3	fontannaPotop	O
4	2	O
5	10-2013.jpg|View	O
6	from	O
7	the	O
8	foutain	B-LOC
9	``	I-LOC
10	Deluge	I-LOC
11	''	I-LOC

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	described	O
3	by	O
4	Warren	B-PER
5	in	O
6	1892	O
7	.	O

0	Varghese	B-PER
1	Payyappilly	I-PER
2	Palakkappilly	I-PER

0	It	O
1	sold	O
2	184,000	O
3	in	O
4	traditional	O
5	album	O
6	sales	O
7	(	O
8	down	O
9	65	O
10	percent	O
11	)	O
12	and	O
13	was	O
14	beaten	O
15	to	O
16	the	O
17	top	O
18	by	O
19	Adele	B-PER
20	's	O
21	25	B-ORG
22	''	O
23	,	O
24	which	O
25	debuted	O
26	at	O
27	number	O
28	one	O
29	with	O
30	a	O
31	record-breaking	O
32	3.38	O
33	million	O
34	.	O

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	born	O
3	in	O
4	in	O
5	Sundridge	B-LOC
6	,	I-LOC
7	Ontario	I-LOC
8	.	O

0	Super	B-ORG
1	League	I-ORG
2	Greece	I-ORG
3	:	O
4	1982–83	B-ORG

0	Guy	B-PER
1	Berryman	I-PER
2	(	O
3	Coldplay	B-ORG
4	)	O

0	Jason	B-PER
1	Schwartzman	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Isabelle	B-PER
4	Huppert	I-PER
5	,	O
6	Dustin	B-PER
7	Hoffman	I-PER

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Lena	B-PER
3	Springs	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	He	O
1	is	O
2	a	O
3	former	O
4	England	B-ORG
5	under-21	I-ORG
6	international	I-ORG
7	.	O

0	Clement	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	Alexandria	I-PER
3	,	O
4	''Stromata	O
5	''	O
6	1.131.6	O
7	.	O

0	Human	B-ORG
1	Rights	I-ORG
2	Commission	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Malaysia	I-ORG

0	The	O
1	elevation	O
2	is	O
3	3944	O
4	feet	O
5	(	O
6	1202	O
7	m	O
8	)	O
9	above	B-ORG
10	sea	I-ORG
11	level	I-ORG
12	.	O

0	Jean	B-PER
1	Frédéric	I-PER
2	Frenet	I-PER

0	**	O
1	''	O
2	Duchy	B-LOC
3	of	I-LOC
4	Naples	I-LOC
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	–	O
8	Gregory	B-PER
9	III	I-PER
10	(	O
11	864–870	O
12	)	O

0	Poland	B-LOC
1	in	I-LOC
2	the	I-LOC
3	Eurovision	I-LOC
4	Song	I-LOC
5	Contest	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Space	B-ORG
2	Heater	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	album	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG
6	''	O

0	Thompson	B-ORG
1	International	I-ORG
2	Speedway	I-ORG
3	–	O
4	Thompson	B-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Connecticut	I-LOC

0	Recorded	O
1	at	O
2	Alberts	B-ORG
3	Studio	I-ORG
4	,	O
5	London	B-LOC
6	.	O

0	West	B-LOC
1	Herzegovina	I-LOC
2	Canton	I-LOC

0	Ili	B-LOC
1	Kazakh	I-LOC
2	Autonomous	I-LOC
3	Prefecture	I-LOC

0	**London	O
1	:	O
2	Thames	B-ORG
3	&	I-ORG
4	Hudson	I-ORG
5	.	O

0	Takht	B-ORG
1	Sri	I-ORG
2	Hazur	I-ORG
3	Sahib	I-ORG
4	,	O
5	Nanded	B-LOC

0	lifebelt]]s	O
1	that	O
2	survived	O
3	the	O
4	sinking	O
5	is	O
6	on	O
7	display	O
8	at	O
9	the	O
10	Imperial	B-ORG
11	War	I-ORG
12	Museum	I-ORG
13	North	I-ORG
14	in	O
15	Manchester	B-LOC

0	His	O
1	father	O
2	was	O
3	Abd	B-PER
4	Manaf	I-PER
5	ibn	I-PER
6	Qusai	I-PER
7	.	O

0	Borg	B-ORG
1	El	I-ORG
2	Arab	I-ORG
3	Stadium	I-ORG
4	,	O
5	Alexandria	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	Egypt	B-LOC

0	``	O
1	A	B-ORG
2	Different	I-ORG
3	Corner	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	1283	O
1	:	O
2	The	O
3	Yuan	B-ORG
4	Dynasty	I-ORG
5	claim	O
6	possession	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	Penghu	B-ORG
10	Islands	I-ORG

0	Alain	B-PER
1	Delon	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Richard	B-PER
4	Conte	I-PER
5	,	O
6	Carla	B-PER
7	Gravina	I-PER

0	**Monarch	O
1	-	O
2	George	B-PER
3	V	I-PER
4	,	O
5	King	B-ORG
6	of	I-ORG
7	the	I-ORG
8	United	I-ORG
9	Kingdom	I-ORG
10	(	O
11	1910–1936	O
12	)	O

0	Helene	B-PER
1	Hayman	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	Baroness	I-PER
4	Hayman	I-PER

0	``	O
1	You	B-ORG
2	're	I-ORG
3	the	I-ORG
4	Voice	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	A	O
1	few	O
2	months	O
3	later	O
4	two	O
5	planes	O
6	,	O
7	one	O
8	of	O
9	them	O
10	named	O
11	''Atlântico	O
12	''	O
13	,	O
14	were	O
15	sent	O
16	by	O
17	ship	O
18	to	O
19	Montevideo	B-LOC
20	and	O
21	flown	O
22	to	O
23	Buenos	B-LOC
24	Aires	I-LOC
25	.	O

0	New	B-ORG
1	York	I-ORG
2	State	I-ORG
3	Route	I-ORG
4	5	I-ORG

0	Des	B-ORG
1	pères	I-ORG
2	,	I-ORG
3	des	I-ORG
4	hommes	I-ORG
5	et	I-ORG
6	des	I-ORG
7	frères	I-ORG

0	Two	B-ORG
1	and	I-ORG
2	a	I-ORG
3	Half	I-ORG
4	Men	I-ORG

0	Before	O
1	1945	O
2	the	O
3	area	O
4	was	O
5	part	O
6	of	O
7	Germany	B-LOC
8	.	O

0	5000-meter	B-ORG
1	run	I-ORG
2	–	O
3	14:15.61	O
4	(	O
5	2015	O
6	)	O

0	Sridevi	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Sanjay	B-PER
3	Dutt	I-PER
4	,	O
5	Rahul	B-PER
6	Roy	I-PER

0	Miranda	B-PER
1	Martino	I-PER
2	as	O
3	the	O
4	Singer	O

0	Communist	B-ORG
1	Party	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	Nigeria	I-ORG
4	(	O
5	CPN	O
6	)	O

0	**	O
1	''	O
2	Chaetodon	B-ORG
3	falcula	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	,	O
6	Blackwedged	B-LOC
7	butterflyfish	I-LOC

0	The	O
1	first	O
2	settlers	O
3	arrived	O
4	in	O
5	the	O
6	early	O
7	19th	O
8	century	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	were	O
12	largely	O
13	Quakers	B-ORG
14	,	O
15	Mennonites	B-ORG
16	and	O
17	United	B-ORG
18	Empire	I-ORG
19	Loyalists	I-ORG
20	who	O
21	had	O
22	left	O
23	the	O
24	United	B-LOC
25	States	I-LOC
26	.	O

0	Republic	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	Ezo	I-LOC
3	(	O
4	1868–1869	O
5	)	O

0	Hul	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Nové	I-LOC
3	Zámky	I-LOC
4	District	I-LOC

0	Estadio	B-ORG
1	Tiburcio	I-ORG
2	Carías	I-ORG
3	Andino	I-ORG
4	Tegucigalpa	B-LOC
5	,	O
6	Honduras	B-LOC

0	Bokówka	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Podlaskie	I-LOC
3	Voivodeship	I-LOC

0	Robert	B-PER
1	A.	I-PER
2	Borski	I-PER
3	,	I-PER
4	Jr	I-PER
5	.	I-PER

0	Perry	B-LOC
1	Township	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Fayette	I-LOC
4	County	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Ohio	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Tsardom	B-LOC
2	of	I-LOC
3	Russia	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	–	O
7	Feodor	B-PER
8	III	I-PER
9	(	O
10	1676–1682	O
11	)	O

0	St	B-ORG
1	George	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	,	I-ORG
4	University	I-ORG
5	of	I-ORG
6	London	I-ORG
7	(	O
8	SGUL	O
9	)	O

0	Wales	B-ORG
1	national	I-ORG
2	football	I-ORG
3	team	I-ORG

0	*wisent	O
1	(	O
2	Bison	B-ORG
3	bonasus	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	)	O

0	Warrandyte	B-LOC
1	South	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Victoria	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Prochoreutis	B-LOC
2	stellaris	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Zeller	O
6	,	O
7	1847	O
8	)	O

0	UEFA	B-ORG
1	Cup	I-ORG
2	winner	O
3	1981	B-ORG
4	.	O

0	In	O
1	1926	O
2	he	O
3	was	O
4	promoted	O
5	to	O
6	the	O
7	rank	O
8	of	O
9	Marshal	B-PER
10	of	I-PER
11	Italy	I-PER
12	.	O

0	Her	O
1	grandson	O
2	Stanley	B-PER
3	Eric	I-PER
4	Francis	I-PER
5	Booth-Clibborn	I-PER
6	became	O
7	the	O
8	Anglican	B-ORG
9	Bishop	B-LOC
10	of	I-LOC
11	Manchester	I-LOC
12	.	O

0	It	O
1	will	O
2	serve	O
3	the	O
4	suburb	O
5	of	O
6	Murrumba	B-ORG
7	Downs	I-ORG
8	in	O
9	the	O
10	Moreton	B-LOC
11	Bay	I-LOC
12	Region	I-LOC
13	.	O

0	Lawrence	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	Rome	I-PER

0	The	B-ORG
1	Larry	I-ORG
2	Sanders	I-ORG
3	Show	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	Coming	O
1	on	O
2	twice	O
3	as	O
4	a	O
5	substitute	O
6	,	O
7	he	O
8	was	O
9	selected	O
10	to	O
11	start	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	semi-final	O
15	loss	O
16	to	O
17	Brazil	B-ORG
18	.	O

0	''	O
1	September	O
2	7	O
3	''	O
4	–	O
5	Little	B-PER
6	Shop	I-PER

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	in	O
3	Division	B-LOC
4	No.	I-LOC
5	6	I-LOC
6	,	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	Bay	B-LOC
10	of	I-LOC
11	Exploits	I-LOC
12	.	O

0	Alexander	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	Hales	I-PER
3	,	O
4	(	O
5	died	O
6	1245	O
7	)	O

0	Louis	B-PER
1	Eppolito	I-PER
2	and	I-PER
3	Stephen	I-PER
4	Caracappa	I-PER

0	Yale	B-LOC
1	Township	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Valley	I-LOC
4	County	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Nebraska	I-LOC

0	''Slavonija	O
1	''	O
2	:	O
3	Slavonia	B-LOC

0	John	B-PER
1	Steven	I-PER
2	Sutherland	I-PER
3	(	O
4	born	O
5	11	O
6	March	O
7	1983	O
8	)	O

0	K.	B-ORG
1	S.	I-ORG
2	Rangasamy	I-ORG
3	College	I-ORG
4	of	I-ORG
5	Technology	I-ORG

0	St.	B-ORG
1	Mary	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	College	I-ORG
4	,	I-ORG
5	Kegalle	I-ORG

0	*Liam	O
1	references	O
2	Lucky	B-PER
3	Charms	I-PER
4	.	O

0	Classic	B-ORG
1	Gold	I-ORG
2	Marcher	I-ORG
3	,	O
4	Wrexham	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	Chester	B-LOC

0	DRS	B-ORG
1	1	I-ORG
2	-	O
3	101.5	O
4	MHz	O
5	(	O
6	60	O
7	kW	O
8	)	O

0	Marvin	B-PER
1	Dunnette	I-PER
2	,	O
3	University	B-ORG
4	of	I-ORG
5	Minnesota	I-ORG

0	Get	B-ORG
1	off	I-ORG
2	the	I-ORG
3	Stage	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Şımarık	B-ORG
2	''	O
3	–	O
4	Tarkan	B-PER

0	GMA	B-ORG
1	Network	I-ORG
2	was	O
3	also	O
4	reportedly	O
5	planning	O
6	to	O
7	bid	O
8	but	O
9	backed	O
10	out	O
11	;	O
12	it	O
13	however	O
14	denied	O
15	that	O
16	they	O
17	offered	O
18	a	O
19	bid	O
20	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Slobodan	B-PER
3	Živojinović	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	7–6	O
7	6–3	O
8	6–4	O

0	K.	B-ORG
1	Stade	I-ORG
2	Leuven	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	1903—2002	O
5	)	O

0	Patrick	B-PER
1	Ryan	I-PER
2	(	I-PER
3	Irish	I-PER
4	priest	I-PER
5	)	I-PER

0	Image	O
1	:	O
2	V02p108001	O
3	Esnoga	B-ORG
4	,	O
5	Amsterdam	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	Netherlands	B-LOC

0	''	O
1	Graphium	B-LOC
2	endochus	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Boisduval	O
6	,	O
7	1836	O
8	)	O

0	Circuit	B-ORG
1	rider	I-ORG
2	(	I-ORG
3	Technology	I-ORG
4	)	I-ORG

0	Tachibana	B-PER
1	no	I-PER
2	Naramaro	I-PER

0	Rajiv	B-LOC
1	Gandhi	I-LOC
2	International	I-LOC
3	Cricket	I-LOC
4	Stadium	I-LOC

0	-	O
1	Alanya	B-LOC
2	in	O
3	Turkey	B-LOC

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	the	O
3	manager	O
4	of	O
5	Árabe	B-ORG
6	Unido	I-ORG
7	in	O
8	Panama	B-LOC
9	.	O

0	Central	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Tennessee	I-LOC
3	(	O
4	CDP	O
5	)	O

0	*20px	O
1	Indiana	B-ORG
2	State	I-ORG
3	Road	I-ORG
4	18	I-ORG

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	known	O
3	from	O
4	Iran	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	Turkmenistan	B-LOC
7	(	O
8	Kopet	B-LOC
9	Dag	I-LOC
10	)	O
11	.	O

0	1–0	O
1	Ewerthon	B-PER
2	(	O
3	28	O
4	)	O

0	2014	B-LOC
1	Women	I-LOC
2	's	I-LOC
3	Futsal	I-LOC
4	World	I-LOC
5	Tournament	I-LOC

0	Guatemalan	B-LOC
1	pygmy	I-LOC
2	owl	I-LOC

0	LAC+USC	B-LOC
1	Medical	I-LOC
2	Center	I-LOC

0	Marion	B-LOC
1	Township	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Hardin	I-LOC
4	County	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Ohio	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Maurie	B-PER
3	Keane	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Northern	B-LOC
1	rough-winged	I-LOC
2	swallow	I-LOC

0	Caroline	B-PER
1	Hedwall	I-PER
2	(	O
3	T12	O
4	)	O

0	Winnie	B-ORG
1	the	I-ORG
2	Pooh	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	franchise	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	Aubrey	B-PER
1	J.	I-PER
2	O'Brien	I-PER

0	Including	O
1	the	O
2	work	O
3	of	O
4	artists	O
5	such	O
6	as	O
7	:	O
8	Edward	B-PER
9	Burne-Jones	I-PER
10	,	O
11	Ford	B-PER
12	Madox	I-PER
13	Brown	I-PER
14	,	O
15	John	B-PER
16	Everett	I-PER
17	Millais	I-PER
18	,	O
19	Dante	B-PER
20	Gabriel	I-PER
21	Rossetti	I-PER
22	,	O
23	William	B-PER
24	Holman	I-PER
25	Hunt	I-PER
26	,	O
27	Arthur	B-PER
28	Hughes	I-PER
29	,	O
30	Frederick	B-PER
31	Sandys	I-PER
32	,	O
33	Simeon	B-PER
34	Solomon	I-PER
35	.	O

0	Weverton	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Maryland	I-LOC

0	Cleinias	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	Tarentum	I-PER

0	The	O
1	eastward	O
2	pressure	O
3	to	O
4	expand	O
5	was	O
6	also	O
7	created	O
8	by	O
9	the	O
10	inability	O
11	to	O
12	move	O
13	westward	O
14	,	O
15	inhibited	O
16	by	O
17	the	O
18	formidable	O
19	presence	O
20	of	O
21	the	O
22	enormous	O
23	Flushing	B-LOC
24	Chinatown	I-LOC
25	(	I-LOC
26	法拉盛華埠	I-LOC
27	)	I-LOC
28	centered	O
29	on	O
30	Main	B-ORG
31	Street	I-ORG
32	.	O

0	Arnold	B-PER
1	Schwarzenegger	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Linda	B-PER
4	Hamilton	I-PER
5	,	O
6	Robert	B-PER
7	Patrick	I-PER
8	,	O
9	Edward	B-PER
10	Furlong	I-PER

0	List	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	national	I-ORG
3	libraries	I-ORG

0	Frederick	B-PER
1	Banbury	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	1st	I-PER
4	Baron	I-PER
5	Banbury	I-PER
6	of	I-PER
7	Southam	I-PER

0	``	O
1	Who	B-ORG
2	Loves	I-ORG
3	You	I-ORG
4	?	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	''Oberst	O
1	''	O
2	Kurt	B-PER
3	Freiherr	I-PER
4	von	I-PER
5	Liebenstein	I-PER
6	,	O
7	21	O
8	December	O
9	1942	O
10	–	O
11	1	O
12	January	O
13	1943	O
14	(	O
15	acting	O
16	leader	O
17	)	O

0	**	O
1	Southern	B-ORG
2	Maryland	I-ORG
3	Blue	I-ORG
4	Crabs	I-ORG

0	Casey	B-PER
1	Janssen	I-PER
2	(	O
3	6	O
4	)	O

0	List	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	famous	I-ORG
3	Puerto	I-ORG
4	Ricans	I-ORG

0	``	O
1	Simply	O
2	Meant	O
3	to	O
4	Be	O
5	''	O
6	(	O
7	with	O
8	Jennifer	B-PER
9	Warnes	I-PER
10	)	O

0	''	O
1	Rhodophthitus	B-LOC
2	tricoloraria	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Mabille	O
6	,	O
7	1890	O
8	)	O

0	Leo	B-PER
1	II	I-PER
2	of	I-PER
3	Galicia	I-PER

0	William	B-ORG
1	Morrow	I-ORG
2	and	I-ORG
3	Company	I-ORG

0	Wusi	B-LOC
1	Road	I-LOC
2	Subdistrict	I-LOC
3	(	O
4	)	O

0	Jane	B-PER
1	Levy	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Dylan	B-PER
4	Minnette	I-PER
5	,	O
6	Stephen	B-PER
7	Lang	I-PER

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	found	O
3	in	O
4	Costa	B-LOC
5	Rica	I-LOC
6	.	O

0	In	O
1	1841	O
2	the	O
3	population	O
4	of	O
5	Norbury	B-ORG
6	and	I-ORG
7	Roston	I-ORG
8	was	O
9	510	O
10	,	O
11	in	O
12	1895	O
13	there	O
14	were	O
15	414	O
16	inhabitants	O
17	.	O

0	''Written	O
1	by	O
2	William	B-PER
3	Barton	I-PER
4	''	O

0	Lantenay	B-LOC
1	(	O
2	01206	O
3	)	O

0	John	B-PER
1	Reeves	I-PER
2	(	I-PER
3	judge	I-PER
4	)	I-PER

0	La	B-LOC
1	Clotte	I-LOC
2	(	O
3	17113	O
4	)	O

0	Edwin	B-PER
1	S.	I-PER
2	Johnson	I-PER
3	(	O
4	D	O
5	)	O

0	Funahashi	B-PER
1	Seiichi	I-PER
2	(	O
3	December	O
4	25	O
5	,	O
6	1904	O
7	–	O
8	January	O
9	13	O
10	,	O
11	1976	O
12	)	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	known	O
3	from	O
4	Chile	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	AFL]]	O
1	(	O
2	Australian	B-ORG
3	rules	I-ORG
4	)	O

0	Among	O
1	many	O
2	artists	O
3	who	O
4	recorded	O
5	this	O
6	song	O
7	were	O
8	Al	B-PER
9	Jolson	I-PER
10	and	O
11	Billy	B-PER
12	Murray	I-PER
13	.	O

0	**	O
1	''	O
2	Duchy	B-LOC
3	of	I-LOC
4	Aquitaine	I-LOC
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	–	O
8	William	B-PER
9	V	I-PER
10	(	O
11	995–1030	O
12	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	West	B-LOC
3	African	I-LOC
4	lion	I-LOC
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	(	O
8	''P	O
9	.	O

0	''	O
1	The	O
2	Room	O
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Chris	B-PER
6	Waters	I-PER
7	,	O
8	Tom	B-PER
9	Shapiro	I-PER
10	)	O
11	–	O
12	3:40	O

0	Munsee-Delaware	B-LOC
1	Nation	I-LOC
2	Indian	I-LOC
3	Reserve	I-LOC
4	No.	I-LOC
5	1	I-LOC
6	,	O
7	part	O
8	of	O
9	the	O
10	above	O

0	It	O
1	lies	O
2	north-west	O
3	of	O
4	Kowalewo	B-LOC
5	Pomorskie	I-LOC
6	,	O
7	north-west	O
8	of	O
9	Golub-Dobrzyń	B-LOC
10	,	O
11	and	O
12	north-east	O
13	of	O
14	Toruń	B-LOC
15	.	O

0	Bahawalpur	B-ORG
1	Zoo	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	Bahawalpur	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	Punjab	B-ORG

0	Friedrich	B-PER
1	Gilly	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1772–1800	O
4	)	O

0	****	O
1	Longtail	B-LOC
2	stingray	I-LOC
3	(	O
4	''D	O
5	.	O

0	``	O
1	The	O
2	Woman	O
3	Comes	O
4	and	O
5	Goes	O
6	''	O
7	(	O
8	Daryl	B-PER
9	Hall	I-PER
10	)	O
11	3:49	O

0	List	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Orchidaceae	I-ORG
3	genera	I-ORG

0	Clarkston	B-ORG
1	railway	I-ORG
2	station	I-ORG

0	Rimyongsu	B-ORG
1	Sports	I-ORG
2	Club	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	Sariwon	B-LOC
5	)	O

0	Len	B-PER
1	Braund	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1901–1907	O
4	)	O

0	Martin	B-PER
1	Luther	I-PER
2	King	I-PER
3	,	I-PER
4	Jr	I-PER
5	.	I-PER

0	Verner	B-PER
1	Thomé	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1878–1953	O
4	)	O

0	1944	O
1	Presentation	B-ORG
2	Brothers	I-ORG
3	College	I-ORG

0	Jörgen	B-PER
1	Olsson	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Sweden	B-LOC

0	''Also	O
1	see	O
2	:	O
3	Hot	B-ORG
4	100	I-ORG
5	No.	I-ORG
6	1	I-ORG
7	Hits	I-ORG
8	of	I-ORG
9	1979	I-ORG
10	''	O

0	''	O
1	Too	O
2	Many	O
3	Hands	O
4	''	O
5	(	O
6	Randy	B-PER
7	Meisner	I-PER
8	,	O
9	Don	B-PER
10	Felder	I-PER
11	)	O
12	–	O
13	4:43	O

0	Masonic	B-ORG
1	Temple	I-ORG
2	Building	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	Maywood	I-ORG
5	,	I-ORG
6	Illinois	I-ORG
7	)	I-ORG

0	Shake	B-ORG
1	(	I-ORG
2	company	I-ORG
3	)	I-ORG

0	He	O
1	ultimately	O
2	returned	O
3	to	O
4	the	O
5	Boston	B-ORG
6	Globe	I-ORG
7	''	O
8	,	O
9	where	O
10	he	O
11	had	O
12	been	O
13	working	O
14	immediately	O
15	before	O
16	the	O
17	''Tribune	O
18	''	O
19	had	O
20	hired	O
21	him	O
22	.	O

0	''	O
1	Psolos	B-LOC
2	fuligo	I-LOC
3	fuligo	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	—	O
6	''	O
7	'Coon	O
8	''	O
9	'	O

0	Sid	B-PER
1	Wilson	I-PER
2	(	O
3	0	O
4	)	O

0	Jan	B-PER
1	Niklas	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Désirée	B-PER
4	Nosbusch	I-PER

0	**	O
1	Trail	B-LOC
2	of	I-LOC
3	Tears	I-LOC
4	,	O
5	1830–1838	O

0	United	B-ORG
1	States	I-ORG
2	Department	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Labor	I-ORG

0	Jared	B-PER
1	Dudley	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Emeka	B-PER
4	Okafor	I-PER
5	,	O
6	Jason	B-PER
7	Richardson	I-PER
8	(	O
9	9	O
10	)	O

0	The	O
1	first	O
2	3	O
3	songs	O
4	as	O
5	PopCrush	O
6	97.1	O
7	were	O
8	Pitbull	B-PER
9	/	O
10	Christina	B-PER
11	Aguilera	I-PER
12	's	O
13	Feel	B-ORG
14	This	I-ORG
15	Moment	I-ORG
16	''	O
17	,	O
18	Justin	B-PER
19	Timberlake	I-PER
20	's	O
21	Mirrors	B-ORG
22	''	O
23	,	O
24	and	O
25	Rihanna	B-PER
26	's	O
27	Umbrella	B-ORG
28	''	O
29	.	O

0	Tomáš	B-PER
1	Šmíd	I-PER
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	Third	O
5	Round	O
6	)	O

0	Chip	B-PER
1	Robinson	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1986	O
4	)	O

0	**	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	Nanhai	B-ORG
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	–	O
7	Liu	B-PER
8	Yin	I-PER
9	,	O
10	King	B-ORG
11	of	I-ORG
12	Nanhai	I-ORG
13	(	O
14	907–911	O
15	)	O

0	Siege	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Naples	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	542–43	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	Clarence	B-PER
1	Tommerson	I-PER
2	,	O
3	NFL	B-ORG
4	player	O

0	Naco-Mammoth	B-LOC
1	Kill	I-LOC
2	Site	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Angiosperms	B-ORG
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	Communes	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	the	I-LOC
3	Somme	I-LOC
4	department	I-LOC

0	Magnificent	B-LOC
1	snake	I-LOC
2	eel	I-LOC

0	Francisco	B-PER
1	Menéndez	I-PER
2	Márquez	I-PER

0	Beecher	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Michigan	I-LOC
3	–	O
4	$	O
5	13,484	O

0	After	O
1	a	O
2	large	O
3	and	O
4	well	O
5	attended	O
6	funeral	O
7	,	O
8	he	O
9	was	O
10	interred	O
11	in	O
12	Green	B-LOC
13	Lawn	I-LOC
14	Cemetery	I-LOC
15	.	O

0	List	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Indonesian	I-ORG
3	birds	I-ORG
4	:	I-ORG
5	non-passerines	I-ORG

0	Stade	B-LOC
1	du	I-LOC
2	28	I-LOC
3	Septembre	I-LOC
4	,	O
5	Conakry	B-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Gujranwala	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	Musa	B-PER
1	Haji	I-PER
2	Ismail	I-PER
3	Galal	I-PER

0	The	O
1	song	O
2	is	O
3	included	O
4	in	O
5	the	O
6	album	O
7	Yanni	B-ORG
8	Voces	I-ORG
9	''	O
10	.	O

0	K.	B-PER
1	M.	I-PER
2	Seethi	I-PER

0	East	B-LOC
1	Chicago	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Indiana	I-LOC

0	Somerset	B-LOC
1	(	I-LOC
2	town	I-LOC
3	)	I-LOC
4	,	I-LOC
5	Wisconsin	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Mika	B-PER
3	Häkkinen	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	WTUA	B-ORG
1	St.	B-LOC
2	Stephen	I-LOC
3	,	I-LOC
4	South	I-LOC
5	Carolina	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Kolkata	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	Taebong	B-ORG
1	has	O
2	been	O
3	overthrown	O
4	,	O
5	and	O
6	Goryeo	B-ORG
7	established	O
8	in	O
9	the	O
10	Korean	B-ORG
11	peninsula	I-ORG
12	,	O
13	when	O
14	Wang	B-ORG
15	Kon	I-ORG
16	ascends	O
17	the	O
18	throne	O
19	at	O
20	Cheorwon	B-LOC
21	.	O

0	Sergey	B-PER
1	Shoygu	I-PER
2	(	O
3	2012	O
4	)	O

0	Tatem	B-LOC
1	Elementary	I-LOC
2	School	I-LOC
3	,	I-LOC
4	Collingswood	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	NJ	I-LOC

0	Flick	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	the	I-ORG
3	Switch	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	O.	B-PER
1	L.	I-PER
2	Owen	I-PER
3	(	O
4	1898	O
5	)	O

0	1911	O
1	Yeon	B-ORG
2	Building	I-ORG
3	,	O
4	Portland	B-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Oregon	I-LOC

0	``	O
1	O	B-ORG
2	Come	I-ORG
3	All	I-ORG
4	Ye	I-ORG
5	Faithful	I-ORG
6	''	O

0	Conejo	B-LOC
1	Valley	I-LOC
2	Unified	I-LOC
3	School	I-LOC
4	District	I-LOC

0	Dick	B-ORG
1	's	I-ORG
2	Sporting	I-ORG
3	Goods	I-ORG
4	(	O
5	80,000	O
6	ft²	O
7	)	O

0	''	O
1	Acianthera	B-LOC
2	rostellata	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Barb.Rodr	O
6	.	O

0	Calhoun	B-LOC
1	City	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Mississippi	I-LOC

0	Rockhead	B-LOC
1	(	I-LOC
2	fish	I-LOC
3	)	I-LOC

0	Cedar	B-LOC
1	Lawn	I-LOC
2	Cemetery	I-LOC
3	,	I-LOC
4	Paterson	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	New	I-LOC
7	Jersey	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	CONCACAF	B-ORG
2	Champions	I-ORG
3	'	I-ORG
4	Cup	I-ORG
5	:	O
6	'	O
7	''	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	described	O
3	by	O
4	Breuning	B-PER
5	in	O
6	1939	O
7	.	O

0	Pontianak	B-PER
1	(	I-PER
2	folklore	I-PER
3	)	I-PER

0	Myrtle	B-ORG
1	Beach	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	United	B-LOC
4	States	I-LOC

0	Tremoschna	O
1	:	O
2	Třemošná	B-LOC
3	B,60	O

0	How	B-ORG
1	to	I-ORG
2	Save	I-ORG
3	a	I-ORG
4	Life	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Parken	B-ORG
1	,	O
2	Copenhagen	B-LOC
3	(	O
4	H	O
5	)	O

0	Tenerife	B-LOC
1	,	O
2	Canary	B-LOC
3	Islands	I-LOC
4	,	O
5	Spain	B-LOC

0	Sui	B-PER
1	Wenjing	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Han	B-PER
4	Cong	I-PER

0	Now	O
1	under	O
2	control	O
3	of	O
4	482nd	B-ORG
5	Fighter	I-ORG
6	Wing	I-ORG
7	(	O
8	Air	B-ORG
9	Force	I-ORG
10	Reserve	I-ORG
11	Command	I-ORG
12	)	O
13	and	O
14	Detachment	O
15	1	O
16	,	O
17	125th	B-ORG
18	Fighter	I-ORG
19	Wing	I-ORG
20	(	O
21	Florida	B-ORG
22	Air	I-ORG
23	National	I-ORG
24	Guard	I-ORG
25	)	O

0	אֶת	O
1	חֶבְרוֹן	O
2	וְאֶת	O
3	מִגְרָשֶׁהָ	O
4	Hebron	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	its	O
7	periphery	O

0	Voznesensk	B-LOC
1	(	O
2	Вознесенський	O
3	район	O
4	)	O

0	Chimneys	O
1	of	O
2	Poolbeg	B-ORG
3	Generating	I-ORG
4	Station	I-ORG

0	This	B-ORG
1	Hour	I-ORG
2	Has	I-ORG
3	22	I-ORG
4	Minutes	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	cast	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Lucas	B-PER
3	Arnold	I-PER
4	Ker	I-PER
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	'	O
8	''	O
9	Sebastián	B-PER
10	Prieto	I-PER
11	''	O
12	'	O

0	Bernhard	B-ORG
1	Warkentin	I-ORG
2	Homestead	I-ORG

0	She	O
1	currently	O
2	lives	O
3	in	O
4	Los	B-LOC
5	Angeles	I-LOC
6	,	O
7	California	B-LOC
8	.	O

0	Same	O
1	applied	O
2	to	O
3	Polish	B-ORG
4	Americans	I-ORG
5	.	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	discovered	O
3	in	O
4	Oxyrhynchus	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	Princess	B-PER
1	Clémentine	I-PER
2	of	I-PER
3	Belgium	I-PER

0	Andrex	B-PER
1	(	I-PER
2	actor	I-PER
3	)	I-PER

0	Martin	B-PER
1	Sheen	I-PER
2	-	O
3	The	B-ORG
4	West	I-ORG
5	Wing	I-ORG
6	''	O

0	``	O
1	U	B-ORG
2	Got	I-ORG
3	It	I-ORG
4	Bad	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Ruanda-Urundi	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	Bright	B-ORG
1	Size	I-ORG
2	Life	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	–	O
5	Pat	B-PER
6	Metheny	I-PER

0	Vulcana	B-PER
1	(	O
2	1875–1946	O
3	)	O

0	Society	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	the	I-PER
3	Friends	I-PER
4	of	I-PER
5	Truth	I-PER

0	Indian	B-LOC
1	flying	I-LOC
2	frog	I-LOC

0	Knightville	B-LOC
1	Dam	I-LOC
2	–	O
3	Westfield	B-LOC
4	River	I-LOC

0	Aborigines	B-ORG
1	'	I-ORG
2	Protection	I-ORG
3	Society	I-ORG

0	Memphrémagog	B-LOC
1	Regional	I-LOC
2	County	I-LOC
3	Municipality	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	CBS	B-ORG
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	*1951	O
1	-	O
2	1980	O
3	Sir	B-PER
4	William	I-PER
5	Rede	I-PER
6	Hawthorne	I-PER

0	Herbert	B-PER
1	Brownell	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	Jr	I-PER
4	.	I-PER

0	George	B-PER
1	Caspar	I-PER
2	Adams	I-PER
3	(	O
4	1863–1900	O
5	)	O

0	Franz	B-PER
1	von	I-PER
2	Papen	I-PER

0	Lee	B-PER
1	Trevino	I-PER
2	won	O
3	the	O
4	most	O
5	tournaments	O
6	,	O
7	six	O
8	.	O

0	East	B-LOC
1	Brunswick	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	New	I-LOC
4	Jersey	I-LOC
5	.	O

0	Dave	B-PER
1	Righetti	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1	O
4	)	O

0	Recorded	O
1	by	O
2	Fats	B-PER
3	Waller	I-PER
4	.	O

0	Previously	O
1	,	O
2	he	O
3	was	O
4	head	O
5	coach	O
6	at	O
7	Alcorn	B-ORG
8	State	I-ORG
9	University	I-ORG
10	and	O
11	an	O
12	assistant	O
13	coach	O
14	at	O
15	Tulane	B-ORG
16	,	O
17	Delta	B-ORG
18	State	I-ORG
19	,	O
20	LSU	B-ORG
21	,	O
22	Florida	B-ORG
23	,	O
24	Marshall	B-ORG
25	,	O
26	Southern	B-ORG
27	Miss	I-ORG
28	,	O
29	Ole	B-ORG
30	Miss	I-ORG
31	,	O
32	Michigan	B-ORG
33	,	O
34	and	O
35	Memphis	B-LOC
36	.	O

0	Five	O
1	years	O
2	later	O
3	,	O
4	in	O
5	1939	O
6	,	O
7	Edern	B-LOC
8	was	O
9	abolished	O
10	and	O
11	incorporated	O
12	into	O
13	Nefyn	B-LOC
14	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Second	O
3	:	O
4	'	O
5	''	O
6	Kaho	B-PER
7	Onodera	I-PER

0	Leopold	B-PER
1	,	I-PER
2	Grand	I-PER
3	Duke	I-PER
4	of	I-PER
5	Baden	I-PER

0	Oriole	B-ORG
1	Park	I-ORG
2	at	I-ORG
3	Camden	I-ORG
4	Yards	I-ORG
5	in	O
6	Baltimore	B-ORG
7	,	I-ORG
8	Maryland	I-ORG
9	,	O
10	United	B-LOC
11	States	I-LOC

0	Massachusetts	B-ORG
1	Route	I-ORG
2	3A	I-ORG

0	Fulvio	B-PER
1	Ballabio	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1988	O
4	)	O

0	Meigs	B-LOC
1	Township	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Muskingum	I-LOC
4	County	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Ohio	I-LOC

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	born	O
3	in	O
4	Glasgow	B-LOC
5	,	O
6	Scotland	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	Gmina	B-LOC
1	Tarnów	I-LOC
2	Opolski	I-LOC

0	Hernán	B-PER
1	Cortés	I-PER
2	was	O
3	his	O
4	relative	O
5	,	O
6	whom	O
7	he	O
8	accompanied	O
9	to	O
10	Mexico	B-LOC
11	(	O
12	New	B-LOC
13	Spain	I-LOC
14	)	O
15	in	O
16	1526	O
17	.	O

0	File	O
1	:	O
2	Tiananmen	B-ORG
3	(	O
4	天安门	O
5	)	O

0	Episode	O
1	:	O
2	``	O
3	It	B-ORG
4	's	I-ORG
5	My	I-ORG
6	Party	I-ORG
7	and	I-ORG
8	I	I-ORG
9	'll	I-ORG
10	Lie	I-ORG
11	if	I-ORG
12	I	I-ORG
13	Want	I-ORG
14	To	I-ORG
15	''	O

0	He	O
1	is	O
2	a	O
3	son	O
4	of	O
5	Alan	B-PER
6	Lennox-Boyd	I-PER
7	,	I-PER
8	1st	I-PER
9	Viscount	I-PER
10	Boyd	I-PER
11	of	I-PER
12	Merton	I-PER
13	.	O

0	He	O
1	died	O
2	on	O
3	August	O
4	25	O
5	,	O
6	1992	O
7	in	O
8	Boca	B-LOC
9	Raton	I-LOC
10	,	I-LOC
11	Florida	I-LOC
12	.	O

0	''	O
1	Nothin	B-LOC
2	'	I-LOC
3	But	I-LOC
4	Trouble	I-LOC
5	''	O
6	(	O
7	1988	O
8	)	O

0	Lynn	B-LOC
1	Township	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	McLeod	I-LOC
4	County	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Minnesota	I-LOC

0	Communes	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	the	I-LOC
3	Côte-d'Or	I-LOC
4	department	I-LOC

0	He	O
1	resides	O
2	in	O
3	Monmouth	B-LOC
4	Junction	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	New	I-LOC
7	Jersey	I-LOC
8	.	O

0	FM	B-ORG
1	Radio	I-ORG
2	Gods	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Aztec	B-LOC
2	Empire	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O
5	–	O
6	Tenoch	B-PER
7	,	O
8	Great	B-ORG
9	Speaker	I-ORG
10	(	O
11	1325–1376	O
12	)	O

0	J.	B-PER
1	R.	I-PER
2	R.	I-PER
3	Tolkien	I-PER

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Speed	B-ORG
3	Up	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	*36th	O
1	on	O
2	10	O
3	November	O
4	2005	O
5	,	O
6	Calgary	B-LOC
7	CAN	B-LOC

0	He	O
1	graduated	O
2	in	O
3	1970	O
4	with	O
5	a	O
6	Doctor	B-ORG
7	of	I-ORG
8	veterinary	I-ORG
9	medicine	I-ORG
10	degree	O
11	from	O
12	the	O
13	Ontario	B-ORG
14	Veterinary	I-ORG
15	College	I-ORG
16	,	O
17	University	B-ORG
18	of	I-ORG
19	Guelph	I-ORG
20	in	O
21	nearby	O
22	Guelph	B-LOC
23	,	O
24	Ontario	B-LOC
25	.	O

0	Paul	B-PER
1	Tang	I-PER
2	(	O
3	2007	O
4	)	O

0	Melissa	B-PER
1	Hayden	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1945–1947	O
4	)	O

0	Waveguide	B-LOC
1	(	I-LOC
2	optics	I-LOC
3	)	I-LOC

0	Las	B-LOC
1	Cruces	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	New	I-LOC
4	Mexico	I-LOC

0	Radu	B-PER
1	Albot	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Artem	B-PER
4	Sitak	I-PER
5	,	O
6	6–4	O
7	,	O
8	7–6	O
9	(	O
10	7–3	O
11	)	O

0	``	O
1	by	O
2	Arthur	B-PER
3	Byron	I-PER
4	Cover	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Aletia	B-LOC
2	infrargyrea	I-LOC
3	''	O

0	The	B-ORG
1	Dirty	I-ORG
2	Dozen	I-ORG
3	Brass	I-ORG
4	Band	I-ORG

0	Márcio	B-PER
1	Rogério	I-PER
2	de	I-PER
3	Andrade	I-PER

0	Marshal	B-ORG
1	(	I-ORG
2	Japan	I-ORG
3	)	I-ORG

0	Cephissus	B-LOC
1	(	I-LOC
2	Athenian	I-LOC
3	plain	I-LOC
4	)	I-LOC

0	Francis	B-PER
1	Wayland	I-PER
2	Parker	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Valsa	B-LOC
2	ceratosperma	I-LOC
3	''	O

0	St	B-ORG
1	Ann	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	College	I-ORG

0	``	O
1	I	B-ORG
2	Promise	I-ORG
3	to	I-ORG
4	Wait	I-ORG
5	My	I-ORG
6	Love	I-ORG
7	''	O

0	National	B-ORG
1	Nursing	I-ORG
2	Week	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	United	B-LOC
5	States	I-LOC
6	)	O

0	The	B-ORG
1	Outdoor	I-ORG
2	Room	I-ORG

0	Hell	B-ORG
1	:	I-ORG
2	The	I-ORG
3	Sequel	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	educated	O
3	at	O
4	the	O
5	Community	B-ORG
6	High	I-ORG
7	School	I-ORG
8	,	I-ORG
9	Tehran	I-ORG
10	and	O
11	then	O
12	Carlisle	B-ORG
13	Technical	I-ORG
14	College	I-ORG
15	.	O

0	In	O
1	1960	O
2	,	O
3	he	O
4	joined	O
5	the	O
6	U.S.	B-ORG
7	Army	I-ORG
8	,	O
9	being	O
10	stationed	O
11	in	O
12	Germany	B-LOC
13	for	O
14	three	O
15	years	O
16	.	O

0	Beijing	B-ORG
1	No.8	I-ORG
2	High	I-ORG
3	School	I-ORG

0	Lacs	B-LOC
1	de	I-LOC
2	Conzieu	I-LOC

0	Monmouth	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Illinois	I-LOC
3	–	O
4	$	O
5	15,839	O

0	Eastern	B-LOC
1	Anatolia	I-LOC
2	Region	I-LOC

0	He	O
1	died	O
2	in	O
3	July	O
4	of	O
5	1969	O
6	in	O
7	Williamsport	B-LOC
8	,	I-LOC
9	Pennsylvania	I-LOC
10	.	O

0	''Review	O
1	:	O
2	Something	O
3	Better	O
4	to	O
5	Come	O
6	''	O
7	at	O
8	Slant	B-ORG
9	Magazine	I-ORG

0	Returning	O
1	to	O
2	Norfolk	B-LOC
3	,	I-LOC
4	Virginia	I-LOC
5	,	O
6	1	O
7	April	O
8	1946	O
9	,	O
10	''Calamares	O
11	''	O
12	was	O
13	decommissioned	O
14	at	O
15	Baltimore	B-ORG
16	,	I-ORG
17	Maryland	I-ORG
18	,	O
19	25	O
20	April	O
21	1946	O
22	,	O
23	and	O
24	returned	O
25	to	O
26	the	O
27	War	B-ORG
28	Shipping	I-ORG
29	Administration	I-ORG
30	.	O

0	Platon	B-PER
1	(	I-PER
2	Kulbusch	I-PER
3	)	I-PER

0	Southampton	B-ORG
1	F.C	I-ORG
2	.	I-ORG

0	Chuuk	B-LOC
1	flying	I-LOC
2	fox	I-LOC

0	John	B-PER
1	Holles	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	2nd	I-PER
4	Earl	I-PER
5	of	I-PER
6	Clare	I-PER

0	The	O
1	Churches	B-ORG
2	Conservation	I-ORG
3	Trust	I-ORG
4	now	O
5	cares	O
6	for	O
7	the	O
8	building	O
9	.	O

0	They	O
1	originate	O
2	from	O
3	South	B-LOC
4	Asia	I-LOC
5	,	O
6	Europe	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	Middle	B-LOC
9	East	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	and	O
12	East	B-LOC
13	Africa	I-LOC
14	.	O

0	Growing	B-ORG
1	Up	I-ORG
2	(	I-ORG
3	The	I-ORG
4	T.G.I.S.	I-ORG
5	Primetime	I-ORG
6	)	I-ORG

0	Following	O
1	its	O
2	sale	O
3	by	O
4	the	O
5	New	B-ORG
6	Zealand	I-ORG
7	Railways	I-ORG
8	Corporation	I-ORG
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1990s	O
12	,	O
13	the	O
14	building	O
15	was	O
16	turned	O
17	into	O
18	student	O
19	accommodation	O
20	by	O
21	Auckland	B-ORG
22	University	I-ORG
23	and	O
24	since	O
25	2008	O
26	has	O
27	been	O
28	occupied	O
29	by	O
30	private	O
31	apartments	O
32	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	With	O
3	Chet	B-PER
4	Baker	I-PER
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	Çıraqlı	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Lachin	I-LOC

0	Sağkaya	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Ceyhan	I-LOC

0	He	O
1	is	O
2	from	O
3	Andhra	B-LOC
4	Pradesh	I-LOC
5	in	O
6	South	B-LOC
7	India	I-LOC
8	.	O

0	53d	B-ORG
1	Wing	I-ORG
2	(	O
3	53	O
4	WG	O
5	)	O

0	Oda	B-ORG
1	Station	I-ORG
2	(	I-ORG
3	Shimane	I-ORG
4	)	I-ORG
5	(	O
6	小田駅	O
7	)	O

0	Tales	B-ORG
1	from	I-ORG
2	Turnpike	I-ORG
3	House	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	Aboudeïa	B-ORG
1	–	O
2	Salamat	B-LOC
3	Region	I-LOC

0	Gibaeksan	B-LOC
1	(	I-LOC
2	South	I-LOC
3	Gyeongsang	I-LOC
4	)	I-LOC

0	Rufus	B-PER
1	Choate	I-PER
2	(	O
3	W-MA	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Tony	B-PER
3	Albright	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Live	B-ORG
1	-	O
2	``	O
3	Run	B-ORG
4	to	I-ORG
5	the	I-ORG
6	Water	I-ORG
7	''	O

0	Kunio	B-PER
1	Maekawa	I-PER
2	,	O
3	architect	O

0	''	O
1	Kingdom	B-LOC
2	of	I-LOC
3	Scotland	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	–	O
7	William	B-PER
8	the	I-PER
9	Lion	I-PER
10	(	O
11	1165–1214	O
12	)	O

0	2008	O
1	:	O
2	Janusz	B-PER
3	Morgenstern	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Platanthera	B-LOC
2	bifolia	I-LOC
3	''	O

0	He	O
1	spent	O
2	much	O
3	of	O
4	his	O
5	career	O
6	with	O
7	Swindon	B-ORG
8	Town	I-ORG
9	,	O
10	for	O
11	whom	O
12	he	O
13	played	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	Premier	B-ORG
17	League	I-ORG
18	.	O

0	The	O
1	Eastwood	B-ORG
2	Westminster	I-ORG
3	constituency	I-ORG
4	was	O
5	created	O
6	in	O
7	1983	O
8	,	O
9	and	O
10	the	O
11	Eastwood	B-ORG
12	Holyrood	I-ORG
13	constituency	I-ORG
14	,	O
15	with	O
16	the	O
17	same	O
18	boundaries	O
19	,	O
20	in	O
21	1999	O
22	.	O

0	UEFA	B-LOC
1	Women	I-LOC
2	's	I-LOC
3	Euro	I-LOC
4	2013	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Toulouse	B-LOC
2	''	O
3	'	O

0	Rupert	B-PER
1	Hamer	I-PER
2	,	O
3	LL.M.	O
4	,	O
5	MLC	O

0	Ka-Zar	B-PER
1	''	O
2	vol	O
3	.	O

0	Masters	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	Darts	I-PER
3	(	O
4	1	O
5	)	O

0	Time	B-ORG
1	Stays	I-ORG
2	,	I-ORG
3	We	I-ORG
4	Go	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Listed	B-ORG
1	buildings	I-ORG
2	in	I-ORG
3	Crawley	I-ORG

0	Michel-Ange	B-PER
1	Duquesne	I-PER
2	de	I-PER
3	Menneville	I-PER
4	(	O
5	1752–1755	O
6	)	O

0	Poříčí	B-LOC
1	nad	I-LOC
2	Sázavou	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Celaenorrhinus	B-LOC
2	homeyeri	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Plötz	O
6	,	O
7	1880	O
8	)	O

0	J.	B-PER
1	J.	B-PER
2	Johnson	I-PER
3	and	O
4	Kai	B-PER
5	Winding	I-PER

0	Francisco	B-PER
1	del	I-PER
2	Rosario	I-PER
3	Sánchez	I-PER
4	,	O
5	Juan	B-PER
6	Pablo	I-PER
7	Duarte	I-PER
8	and	O
9	Matías	B-PER
10	Ramón	I-PER
11	Mella	I-PER

0	Rupert	B-PER
1	Young	I-PER
2	as	O
3	Sir	B-PER
4	William	I-PER
5	Herbert	I-PER
6	,	I-PER
7	Lord	I-PER
8	Pembroke	I-PER

0	Johannes	B-PER
1	V.	I-PER
2	Jensen	I-PER

0	Sean	B-PER
1	Paul	I-PER
2	Lockhart	I-PER

0	Montreal	B-LOC
1	West	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Quebec	I-LOC

0	Văn	B-LOC
1	Lãng	I-LOC
2	District	I-LOC

0	67	O
1	competitors	O
2	were	O
3	selected	O
4	by	O
5	the	O
6	DLV	B-ORG
7	.	O

0	Kalbar	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Queensland	I-LOC

0	Bobby	B-ORG
1	's	I-ORG
2	Burger	I-ORG
3	Palace	I-ORG

0	Beulah	B-PER
1	Bondi	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1888–1981	O
4	)	O

0	Pelican	B-LOC
1	Rapids	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Minnesota	I-LOC
4	–	O
5	$	O
6	13,699	O

0	This	O
1	was	O
2	published	O
3	by	O
4	the	O
5	American	B-ORG
6	Mathematical	I-ORG
7	Society	I-ORG
8	as	O
9	ISSN	O
10	0038-5573	O
11	.	O

0	Trilofo	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Arcadia	I-LOC

0	Melissa	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Texas	I-LOC

0	''The	B-ORG
1	Times	I-ORG
2	''	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	Chicago	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG
6	,	O
7	went	O
8	defunct	O
9	in	O
10	2005	O

0	Laurence	B-PER
1	Helsby	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	Baron	I-PER
4	Helsby	I-PER

0	Ronaldinho	B-ORG
1	Gaucho	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	Team	I-ORG

0	Rüppell	B-LOC
1	's	I-LOC
2	robin-chat	I-LOC

0	Thomas	B-LOC
1	's	I-LOC
2	pine	I-LOC
3	vole	I-LOC

0	Tennessee	B-ORG
1	in	I-ORG
2	the	I-ORG
3	Civil	I-ORG
4	War	I-ORG

0	Minarete	B-ORG
1	Brass	I-ORG
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	2010	O
5	)	O

0	*2008	O
1	–	O
2	``	O
3	All	B-ORG
4	Summer	I-ORG
5	Long	I-ORG
6	''	O
7	–	O
8	Kid	B-PER
9	Rock	I-PER

0	Hamdan	B-PER
1	bin	I-PER
2	Mubarak	I-PER
3	Al	I-PER
4	Nahyan	I-PER

0	It	B-ORG
1	's	I-ORG
2	No	I-ORG
3	Good	I-ORG

0	DCLXVI	B-ORG
1	:	I-ORG
2	To	I-ORG
3	Ride	I-ORG
4	Shoot	I-ORG
5	Straight	I-ORG
6	and	I-ORG
7	Speak	I-ORG
8	the	I-ORG
9	Truth	I-ORG
10	''	O

0	McCoy	B-ORG
1	''	O
2	(	O
3	1975-1976	O
4	)	O

0	The	B-ORG
1	Price	I-ORG
2	Is	I-ORG
3	Right	I-ORG
4	(	I-ORG
5	Philippine	I-ORG
6	game	I-ORG
7	show	I-ORG
8	)	I-ORG
9	''	O

0	***	O
1	''	O
2	Northern	B-LOC
3	March	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	–	O
7	Lothair	B-PER
8	(	O
9	983–1003	O
10	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Kentucky	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	He	O
1	claimed	O
2	to	O
3	be	O
4	son	O
5	of	O
6	Khalilullah	B-PER
7	II	I-PER
8	.	O

0	''	O
1	Dialectica	B-LOC
2	imperialella	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Zeller	O
6	,	O
7	1847	O
8	)	O

0	Royal	B-ORG
1	Australian	I-ORG
2	Corps	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Transport	I-ORG
5	-	O
6	The	B-ORG
7	Princess	I-ORG
8	Royal	I-ORG

0	Johor	B-ORG
1	Bahru	I-ORG
2	City	I-ORG
3	Square	I-ORG

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	known	O
3	from	O
4	Kenya	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	Uganda	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	*9378	O
1	-	O
2	Apamea	B-LOC
3	burgessi	I-LOC
4	''	O

0	Shooting	B-PER
1	guard	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Small	B-PER
4	forward	I-PER

0	Mount	B-ORG
1	Marty	I-ORG
2	College	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	Yankton	B-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	South	I-LOC
7	Dakota	I-LOC
8	)	O

0	Three	B-ORG
1	's	I-ORG
2	a	I-ORG
3	Crowd	I-ORG

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Persiaran	B-ORG
3	APEC	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	''	O
1	Theretra	B-LOC
2	jugurtha	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Boisduval	O
6	,	O
7	1875	O
8	)	O

0	Harvard	B-ORG
1	Business	I-ORG
2	School	I-ORG
3	Press	I-ORG
4	(	O
5	2013	O
6	)	O
7	Managing	O
8	Up	O
9	:	O
10	Expert	O
11	Solutions	O
12	to	O
13	Everyday	O
14	Challenges	O

0	Marysville	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Pennsylvania	I-LOC

0	St.	B-ORG
1	Mary	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	Church	I-ORG
4	,	I-ORG
5	South	I-ORG
6	Stoneham	I-ORG

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	a	O
3	son	O
4	of	O
5	Wolfgang	B-PER
6	Amadeus	I-PER
7	Mozart	I-PER
8	.	O

0	He	O
1	hailed	O
2	from	O
3	Søgne	B-LOC
4	.	O

0	Njego	B-PER
1	Pesa	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1983–87	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Marco	B-PER
3	Melandri	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Sun	B-PER
1	Quan	I-PER
2	:	O
3	Nabatame	B-ORG
4	Hitomi	I-ORG

0	David	B-PER
1	Clarke	I-PER
2	(	I-PER
3	Paralympic	I-PER
4	footballer	I-PER
5	)	I-PER

0	Comanche	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Oklahoma	I-LOC

0	Bova	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Calabria	I-LOC

0	Lamb	B-LOC
1	's	I-LOC
2	Conduit	I-LOC
3	Field	I-LOC

0	Doug	B-PER
1	McClure	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Keith	B-PER
4	Barron	I-PER

0	Howard	B-PER
1	W.	I-PER
2	Hunter	I-PER
3	,	O
4	Boyd	B-PER
5	K.	I-PER
6	Packer	I-PER
7	,	O
8	Marvin	B-PER
9	J.	I-PER
10	Ashton	I-PER
11	,	O
12	L.	B-PER
13	Tom	I-PER
14	Perry	I-PER
15	,	O
16	David	B-PER
17	B.	I-PER
18	Haight	I-PER
19	,	O
20	James	B-PER
21	E.	I-PER
22	Faust	I-PER
23	,	O
24	Neal	B-PER
25	A.	I-PER
26	Maxwell	I-PER
27	,	O
28	Russell	B-PER
29	M.	I-PER
30	Nelson	I-PER
31	,	O
32	Dallin	B-PER
33	H.	I-PER
34	Oaks	I-PER
35	,	O
36	M.	B-PER
37	Russell	I-PER
38	Ballard	I-PER
39	,	O
40	Joseph	B-PER
41	B.	I-PER
42	Wirthlin	I-PER
43	,	O
44	Richard	B-PER
45	G.	I-PER
46	Scott	I-PER

0	``	O
1	I	B-ORG
2	'll	I-ORG
3	Walk	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	Silver	B-ORG
1	Slipper	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	Las	B-LOC
4	Vegas	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Nevada	I-LOC

0	Top	B-ORG
1	Chef	I-ORG
2	:	I-ORG
3	Just	I-ORG
4	Desserts	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	``	O
1	Wake	B-ORG
2	Up	I-ORG
3	Brother	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	Pemba	B-LOC
1	green	I-LOC
2	pigeon	I-LOC

0	The	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	1994	O
4	Big	B-ORG
5	Ten	I-ORG
6	Conference	I-ORG
7	Baseball	I-ORG
8	Tournament	I-ORG
9	''	O
10	'	O
11	was	O
12	held	O
13	at	O
14	C.	B-ORG
15	O.	I-ORG
16	Brown	I-ORG
17	Stadium	I-ORG
18	in	O
19	Battle	B-LOC
20	Creek	I-LOC
21	,	I-LOC
22	Michigan	I-LOC
23	from	O
24	May	O
25	15	O
26	through	O
27	19	O
28	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Robert	B-PER
3	B.	I-PER
4	Mautz	I-PER
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	``	O
1	Carnival	B-ORG
2	''	O
3	–	O
4	Natalie	B-PER
5	Merchant	I-PER

0	Sharif	B-PER
1	Fati	I-PER
2	Ali	I-PER
3	Al	I-PER
4	Mishad	I-PER

0	Prince	B-PER
1	Talal	I-PER
2	bin	I-PER
3	Muhammad	I-PER

0	2000	O
1	-	O
2	Servants	B-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Darkness	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Anne	B-PER
1	McLellan	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1994-1997	O
4	)	O

0	The	O
1	demand	O
2	is	O
3	$	B-ORG
4	.	O

0	Thomas	B-PER
1	Morgan	I-PER
2	(	I-PER
3	MP	I-PER
4	died	I-PER
5	1565	I-PER
6	)	I-PER

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Giancarlo	B-PER
3	Fisichella	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	The	B-ORG
1	People	I-ORG
2	's	I-ORG
3	Petition	I-ORG

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	Mayor	B-PER
3	of	I-PER
4	Exeter	I-PER
5	July	O
6	1414	O
7	to	O
8	October	O
9	1415	O
10	.	O

0	Brays	B-LOC
1	Oaks	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Houston	I-LOC

0	He	O
1	became	O
2	a	O
3	journalist	O
4	for	O
5	The	B-ORG
6	Nashville	I-ORG
7	American	I-ORG
8	''	O
9	,	O
10	serving	O
11	as	O
12	a	O
13	correspondent	O
14	from	O
15	1885	O
16	to	O
17	1892	O
18	.	O

0	Evans	B-LOC
1	Bay	I-LOC
2	is	O
3	nearby	O
4	.	O

0	**	O
1	Basilica	B-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	San	I-ORG
4	Isidoro	I-ORG
5	,	O
6	León	B-LOC
7	,	I-LOC
8	Spain	I-LOC
9	consecrated	O
10	.	O

0	Sir	B-PER
1	Gilbert	I-PER
2	Heathcote	I-PER
3	,	I-PER
4	3rd	I-PER
5	Baronet	I-PER
6	(	O
7	died	O
8	1785	O
9	)	O

0	Lee	B-PER
1	Maye	I-PER
2	,	O
3	LF	O
4	(	O
5	1965-1966	O
6	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Venue	O
3	:	O
4	'	O
5	''	O
6	Daegu	B-ORG
7	Civic	I-ORG
8	Stadium	I-ORG
9	,	O
10	Daegu	B-LOC

0	Policarpo	B-PER
1	Cacherano	I-PER
2	d'Osasco	I-PER

0	Parliamentary	B-ORG
1	elections	I-ORG
2	on	I-ORG
3	22	I-ORG
4	September	I-ORG
5	2002	I-ORG
6	:	O
7	44.1	O
8	%	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	primary	O
12	vote	O

0	''	O
1	Elachista	B-LOC
2	quadripunctella	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Hübner	O
6	,	O
7	1825	O
8	)	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	found	O
3	in	O
4	Cameroon	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	São	B-LOC
7	Tomé	I-LOC
8	and	I-LOC
9	Príncipe	I-LOC
10	.	O

0	Rupert	B-PER
1	Keegan	I-PER
2	took	O
3	the	O
4	B.A.R.C	O
5	.	O

0	Miranda	B-PER
1	Cosgrove	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1993-	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Mark	B-PER
3	Knowles	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	/	O
7	'	O
8	''	O
9	Daniel	B-PER
10	Nestor	I-PER
11	''	O
12	'	O
13	defeated	O
14	Roger	B-PER
15	Federer	I-PER
16	/	O
17	Max	B-PER
18	Mirnyi	I-PER
19	6–4	O
20	,	O
21	6–4	O

0	Uluçınar	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	İmamoğlu	I-LOC

0	José	B-PER
1	Luis	I-PER
2	de	I-PER
3	Arrese	I-PER

0	''65	O
1	Damien	B-PER
2	Woody	I-PER
3	G	O
4	(	O
5	IR	O
6	)	O
7	7px	O

0	Joppatowne	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Maryland	I-LOC

0	John	B-PER
1	Pratt	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	1st	I-PER
4	Marquess	I-PER
5	Camden	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Jackie	B-PER
2	Evancho	I-PER
3	''	O
4	'	O
5	(	O
6	born	O
7	2000	O
8	)	O

0	NALSAR	B-ORG
1	University	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	Law	I-ORG
4	,	O
5	Hyderabad	B-LOC

0	Toronto	B-LOC
1	,	O
2	Ontario	B-LOC
3	-	O
4	CITY	B-ORG

0	``	O
1	Livin	B-ORG
2	'	I-ORG
3	on	I-ORG
4	Borrowed	I-ORG
5	Time	I-ORG
6	''	O

0	José	B-PER
1	Luis	I-PER
2	Reséndez	I-PER

0	Broadcaster	O
1	RAI	B-ORG
2	chose	O
3	the	O
4	song	O
5	and	O
6	performer	O
7	internally	O
8	.	O

0	Mystery	B-ORG
1	Science	I-ORG
2	Theater	I-ORG
3	3000	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	J.	B-PER
1	J.	B-PER
2	Kelso	I-PER

0	Events	O
1	from	O
2	the	O
3	year	O
4	'	O
5	''	O
6	1983	O
7	in	O
8	Sweden	B-LOC
9	''	O
10	'	O

0	Islamic	B-LOC
1	State	I-LOC
2	of	I-LOC
3	Iraq	I-LOC
4	and	I-LOC
5	the	I-LOC
6	Levant	I-LOC
7	:	O
8	2,300	O

0	Byzantium	B-ORG
1	under	I-ORG
2	the	I-ORG
3	Macedonians	I-ORG

0	Johan	B-PER
1	Caspar	I-PER
2	von	I-PER
3	Cicignon	I-PER

0	North	B-LOC
1	Vacherie	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Louisiana	I-LOC

0	1	O
1	:	O
2	``	O
3	No	B-ORG
4	News	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	,	O
7	``	O
8	Come	B-ORG
9	Cryin	I-ORG
10	'	I-ORG
11	to	I-ORG
12	Me	I-ORG
13	''	O
14	,	O
15	``	O
16	Amazed	B-ORG
17	''	O
18	,	O
19	``	O
20	Smile	B-ORG
21	''	O
22	,	O
23	``	O
24	What	B-ORG
25	About	I-ORG
26	Now	I-ORG
27	''	O
28	,	O
29	``	O
30	Tell	B-ORG
31	Her	I-ORG
32	''	O
33	,	O
34	``	O
35	I	B-ORG
36	'm	I-ORG
37	Already	I-ORG
38	There	I-ORG
39	''	O
40	,	O
41	``	O
42	My	B-ORG
43	Front	I-ORG
44	Porch	I-ORG
45	Looking	I-ORG
46	In	I-ORG
47	''	O
48	,	O
49	and	O
50	``	O
51	Mr.	B-ORG
52	Mom	I-ORG
53	''	O
54	.	O

0	Shakira	B-PER
1	–	O
2	``	O
3	Ojos	B-ORG
4	Así	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	North	B-LOC
1	Woodbridge	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	California	I-LOC

0	Simone	B-PER
1	Terenzani	I-PER
2	(	O
3	0,0,1,0,0,1,1,0	O
4	)	O
5	-	O
6	38	O
7	.	O

0	''	O
1	Catocala	B-LOC
2	puerpera	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Giorna	O
6	,	O
7	1791	O
8	)	O

0	List	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	counties	I-LOC
3	in	I-LOC
4	Missouri	I-LOC

0	The	B-ORG
1	Threshold	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	a	I-ORG
4	Persona	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Grapholita	B-LOC
2	funebrana	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	Treitschke	O
5	,	O
6	1835	O

0	Rube	B-PER
1	Ellis	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1911	O
4	)	O

0	*1986	O
1	:	O
2	Herbert	B-PER
3	W.	I-PER
4	Franke	I-PER
5	,	O
6	''Endzeit	O
7	''	O

0	Miranda	B-LOC
1	de	I-LOC
2	Azán	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Bukit	B-LOC
3	Kepong	I-LOC
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Volcanoes	B-LOC
1	National	I-LOC
2	Park	I-LOC
3	,	O
4	Rwanda	B-LOC

0	Terry	B-PER
1	George	I-PER
2	(	I-PER
3	entrepreneur	I-PER
4	)	I-PER

0	Based	O
1	in	O
2	Lille	B-LOC
3	and	O
4	Versailles	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	The	O
1	John	B-ORG
2	Tracy	I-ORG
3	Clinic	I-ORG
4	,	O
5	named	O
6	after	O
7	her	O
8	son	O
9	,	O
10	was	O
11	the	O
12	result	O
13	.	O

0	*The	O
1	Bennington	B-ORG
2	Battle	I-ORG
3	Monument	I-ORG
4	in	O
5	Bennington	B-LOC
6	,	I-LOC
7	Vermont	I-LOC
8	,	O
9	1889	O
10	.	O

0	Westwood	B-ORG
1	College	I-ORG
2	–	O
3	Dallas	B-ORG
4	,	I-ORG
5	Texas	I-ORG

0	Anabelle	B-PER
1	Langlois	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Patrice	B-PER
4	Archetto	I-PER

0	Part	O
1	of	O
2	the	O
3	state-owned	O
4	Main	B-ORG
5	Line	I-ORG
6	of	I-ORG
7	Public	I-ORG
8	Works	I-ORG

0	Madiran	B-ORG
1	Tannat	B-LOC
2	(	O
3	4–12	O
4	yrs	O
5	)	O

0	Mia	B-PER
1	Wasikowska	I-PER
2	as	O
3	Alice	B-PER
4	Kingsleigh	I-PER
5	.	O

0	Alexandru	B-PER
1	Popovici	I-PER
2	(	O
3	2001	O
4	Seongnam	B-ORG
5	Ilhwa	I-ORG
6	Chunma	I-ORG
7	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	If	B-ORG
3	You	I-ORG
4	Ai	I-ORG
5	n't	I-ORG
6	Got	I-ORG
7	a	I-ORG
8	Weapon	I-ORG
9	...	I-ORG
10	''	O

0	It	O
1	consists	O
2	of	O
3	the	O
4	Bundesautobahn	B-ORG
5	3	I-ORG
6	,	O
7	the	O
8	Bundesautobahn	B-ORG
9	4	I-ORG
10	and	O
11	the	O
12	Bundesautobahn	B-ORG
13	1	I-ORG
14	.	O

0	There	O
1	have	O
2	been	O
3	five	O
4	winners	O
5	to	O
6	date	O
7	:	O
8	Leanne	B-PER
9	Mitchell	I-PER
10	,	O
11	Andrea	B-PER
12	Begley	I-PER
13	,	O
14	Jermain	B-PER
15	Jackman	I-PER
16	,	O
17	Stevie	B-ORG
18	McCrorie	I-ORG
19	and	O
20	Kevin	B-PER
21	Simm	I-PER
22	.	O

0	Francesco	B-PER
1	Soto	I-PER
2	de	I-PER
3	Langa	I-PER
4	(	O
5	1534–1619	O
6	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	14	O
3	Porsche	B-ORG
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	''	O

0	He	O
1	subsequently	O
2	worked	O
3	for	O
4	ABC	B-ORG
5	affiliate	O
6	WUTR	B-ORG
7	in	O
8	Utica	B-LOC
9	,	I-LOC
10	New	I-LOC
11	York	I-LOC
12	,	O
13	CBS	B-ORG
14	affiliate	O
15	WTVH	B-ORG
16	in	O
17	Syracuse	B-LOC
18	,	I-LOC
19	New	I-LOC
20	York	I-LOC
21	,	O
22	and	O
23	NBC	B-ORG
24	affiliate	O
25	WCNC-TV	B-ORG
26	in	O
27	Charlotte	B-LOC
28	,	I-LOC
29	North	I-LOC
30	Carolina	I-LOC
31	.	O

0	2013	B-ORG
1	Africa	I-ORG
2	Cup	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Nations	I-ORG
5	qualification	I-ORG

0	There	O
1	were	O
2	two	O
3	main	O
4	branches	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	family	O
8	,	O
9	one	O
10	in	O
11	Dutton	B-LOC
12	and	O
13	the	O
14	other	O
15	in	O
16	Sutton	B-LOC
17	Weaver	I-LOC
18	.	O

0	''	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	After	B-ORG
4	the	I-ORG
5	Love	I-ORG
6	Has	I-ORG
7	Gone	I-ORG
8	''	O
9	Earth	B-ORG
10	,	I-ORG
11	Wind	I-ORG
12	&	I-ORG
13	Fire	I-ORG
14	''	O
15	'	O

0	Decius	B-PER
1	(	O
2	249-251	O
3	)	O

0	Seán	B-PER
1	Óg	I-PER
2	Ó	I-PER
3	hAilpín	I-PER
4	:	O
5	3	O
6	(	O
7	2003	O
8	,	O
9	2004	O
10	,	O
11	2005	O
12	)	O

0	*Has	O
1	made	O
2	several	O
3	trips	O
4	to	O
5	the	O
6	Middle	B-LOC
7	East	I-LOC
8	,	O
9	visiting	O
10	troops	O
11	in	O
12	Iraq	B-LOC
13	and	O
14	Afghanistan	B-LOC
15	,	O
16	as	O
17	well	O
18	as	O
19	visiting	O
20	Kyrgyzstan	B-LOC
21	,	O
22	Afghanistan	B-LOC
23	,	O
24	Kuwait	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	Bahrain	B-LOC
27	,	O
28	Saudi	B-LOC
29	Arabia	I-LOC
30	,	O
31	the	O
32	United	B-LOC
33	Arab	I-LOC
34	Emirates	I-LOC
35	and	O
36	Qatar	B-LOC
37	.	O

0	''	O
1	Last	O
2	Date	O
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Floyd	B-PER
6	Cramer	I-PER
7	)	O
8	–	O
9	2:16	O

0	Giovanni	B-PER
1	Battista	I-PER
2	Buonamente	I-PER

0	Tazmania	B-ORG
1	''	O
2	(	O
3	2006	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Marcello	B-PER
3	Trotta	I-PER
4	'	O
5	''	O

0	2369	O
1	Shickshinny	B-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Pennsylvania	I-LOC
4	$	O
5	14,880	O

0	Patagonian	B-LOC
1	yellow	I-LOC
2	finch	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	President	B-ORG
3	's	I-ORG
4	Cup	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	*Mr.	O
1	Grimby	O
2	-	O
3	Richard	B-PER
4	Dumont	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Tokimeki	B-ORG
2	Memorial	I-ORG
3	:	I-ORG
4	Forever	I-ORG
5	With	I-ORG
6	You	I-ORG
7	''	O

0	*The	O
1	consisted	O
2	of	O
3	Centre	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	Clearfield	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	Lycoming	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	McKean	B-LOC
10	,	O
11	Northumberland	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Potter	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	Tioga	B-LOC
17	Counties	I-LOC

0	Arnaud	B-PER
1	Boetsch	I-PER
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	Second	O
5	round	O
6	)	O
7	''	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Lornna	B-PER
3	Soto	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	It	O
1	premiered	O
2	on	O
3	27	O
4	June	O
5	2010	O
6	on	O
7	YouTube	B-ORG
8	.	O

0	Wesley	B-PER
1	Pritchard	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1996–	O
4	)	O
5	36	O

0	Damon	B-PER
1	Stoudamire	I-PER
2	(	O
3	3,018	O
4	)	O

0	Călineasa	B-LOC
1	River	I-LOC
2	(	I-LOC
3	Someșul	I-LOC
4	Cald	I-LOC
5	)	I-LOC

0	Camille	B-PER
1	Paglia	I-PER
2	compares	O
3	the	O
4	resulting	O
5	image	O
6	to	O
7	William	B-PER
8	Blake	I-PER
9	's	O
10	``	O
11	engravings	O
12	of	O
13	solipsistically	O
14	contorted	O
15	figures	O
16	''	O
17	.	O

0	Assemblyman	O
1	Peter	B-PER
2	J.	I-PER
3	Barnes	I-PER
4	III	I-PER
5	(	O
6	D	O
7	)	O

0	In	O
1	1854	O
2	he	O
3	was	O
4	appointed	O
5	to	O
6	a	O
7	seat	O
8	on	O
9	the	O
10	Legislative	B-ORG
11	Council	I-ORG
12	of	I-ORG
13	Nova	I-ORG
14	Scotia	I-ORG
15	,	O
16	upon	O
17	the	O
18	recommendation	O
19	of	O
20	William	B-PER
21	Young	I-PER
22	.	O

0	Mark	B-PER
1	McGrath	I-PER
2	(	O
3	2010–2011	O
4	)	O

0	Twickenham	B-ORG
1	Stadium	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	London	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	England	B-LOC

0	File	O
1	:	O
2	Southern	B-LOC
3	Italy	I-LOC
4	and	O
5	Sicily	B-LOC
6	on	O
7	the	O
8	1849	O
9	map	O
10	.	O

0	Petersburg	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Virginia	I-LOC

0	His	O
1	descendants	O
2	include	O
3	Vincenzo	B-PER
4	Viviani	I-PER
5	,	O
6	a	O
7	disciple	O
8	and	O
9	biographer	O
10	of	O
11	Galileo	B-PER
12	Galilei	I-PER
13	.	O

0	This	O
1	was	O
2	continued	O
3	by	O
4	his	O
5	sons	O
6	Edgar	B-PER
7	,	O
8	Alexander	B-PER
9	I	I-PER
10	and	O
11	in	O
12	particular	O
13	David	B-PER
14	I	I-PER
15	.	O

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	Sworn	O
3	in	O
4	as	O
5	a	O
6	Member	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	Queen	B-PER
10	's	I-PER
11	Privy	I-PER
12	Council	I-PER
13	for	I-PER
14	Canada	I-PER
15	on	O
16	4	O
17	January	O
18	2011	O
19	.	O

0	She	O
1	was	O
2	the	O
3	youngest-ever	O
4	female	O
5	Member	B-PER
6	of	I-PER
7	Parliament	I-PER
8	.	O

0	The	O
1	song	O
2	was	O
3	recorded	O
4	at	O
5	Grouse	B-ORG
6	Lodge	I-ORG
7	,	O
8	under	O
9	the	O
10	supervision	O
11	of	O
12	producer	O
13	Jacknife	B-PER
14	Lee	I-PER
15	.	O

0	Ronald	B-PER
1	J.	I-PER
2	Garan	I-PER
3	,	I-PER
4	Jr	I-PER
5	.	I-PER
6	Michael	B-PER
7	E.	I-PER
8	Fossum	I-PER

0	San	B-ORG
1	Pedro	I-ORG
2	y	I-ORG
3	San	B-ORG
4	Pablo	I-ORG
5	Asistencia	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Telamoptilia	B-LOC
2	hemistacta	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Meyrick	O
6	,	O
7	1918	O
8	)	O

0	Red	B-LOC
1	knot	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	''Calidris	O
4	canutus	O
5	''	O
6	(	O
7	A	O
8	)	O

0	La	B-LOC
1	Seyne-sur-Mer	I-LOC
2	–	O
3	57,553	O

0	border	O
1	'	O
2	''	O
3	Séamus	B-PER
4	Harnedy	I-PER

0	**	O
1	Western	B-LOC
2	gorilla	I-LOC
3	(	O
4	''G	O
5	.	O

0	Lyraka	B-ORG
1	Volume	I-ORG
2	1	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	2010	O
5	)	O
6	''	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Brunei	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	Hälsingland	B-LOC
1	Rune	I-LOC
2	Inscription	I-LOC
3	21	I-LOC

0	Joe	B-PER
1	Abercrombie	I-PER
2	,	O
3	author	O
4	;	O

0	Judge	B-PER
1	Reinhold	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Fred	B-PER
4	Savage	I-PER

0	Melaleuca	B-LOC
1	delta	I-LOC
2	''	O
3	Craven	B-PER

0	The	B-PER
1	Beatles	I-PER
2	'	I-PER
3	influence	I-PER
4	on	I-PER
5	popular	I-PER
6	culture	I-PER

0	His	O
1	death	O
2	was	O
3	profiled	O
4	in	O
5	an	O
6	episode	O
7	of	O
8	Unsolved	B-ORG
9	Mysteries	I-ORG
10	''	O
11	.	O

0	''	O
1	Agrochola	B-LOC
2	lota	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Clerck	O
6	,	O
7	1759	O
8	)	O

0	Highest	O
1	total	O
2	against	O
3	:	O
4	224	O
5	/	O
6	7	O
7	by	O
8	Somerset	B-ORG
9	at	O
10	Taunton	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	2015	O

0	''	O
1	Mordellistena	B-LOC
2	pseudoparvula	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	Ermisch	O
5	,	O
6	1956	O

0	All	B-ORG
1	Saints	I-ORG
2	Cathedral	I-ORG
3	,	I-ORG
4	Halifax	I-ORG

0	Beginning	O
1	of	O
2	Karoo	B-ORG
3	Ice	I-ORG
4	Age	I-ORG
5	.	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	housed	O
3	in	O
4	the	O
5	Musée	B-ORG
6	du	I-ORG
7	Louvre	I-ORG
8	of	O
9	Paris	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	Lotte	B-ORG
1	Jonathans	I-ORG
2	Paulien	B-PER
3	van	I-PER
4	Dooremalen	I-PER

0	Serra	B-LOC
1	da	I-LOC
2	Estrela	I-LOC
3	Subregion	I-LOC

0	**09621	O
1	Amberg	B-LOC
2	(	I-LOC
3	Oberpfalz	I-LOC
4	)	I-LOC

0	:	O
1	:	O
2	:	O
3	B.	B-LOC
4	''	O

0	The	B-PER
1	Jacksons	I-PER
2	(	I-PER
3	TV	I-PER
4	series	I-PER
5	)	I-PER

0	Reagan	B-LOC
1	County	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Texas	I-LOC

0	E.	B-PER
1	H.	I-PER
2	Shepard	I-PER

0	Communes	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	the	I-LOC
3	Eure-et-Loir	I-LOC
4	department	I-LOC

0	:	O
1	Ashleigh	B-PER
2	Brewer	I-PER
3	(	O
4	2014–	O
5	)	O

0	Nowinki	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Wołomin	I-LOC
3	County	I-LOC

0	Lyrics	O
1	:	O
2	Duncan	B-PER
3	Fallowell	I-PER
4	)	O
5	–	O
6	3:30	O
7	/	O
8	5:41	O

0	*Lifetime	O
1	Achievement	O
2	-	O
3	Arthur	B-PER
4	M.	I-PER
5	Schlesinger	I-PER
6	,	I-PER
7	Jr	I-PER
8	.	I-PER

0	Hans	B-PER
1	Karl	I-PER
2	von	I-PER
3	Diebitsch	I-PER

0	''	O
1	Crombrugghia	B-LOC
2	distans	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Zeller	O
6	,	O
7	1847	O
8	)	O

0	Rob	B-PER
1	Fusari	I-PER
2	–	O
3	composer	O
4	,	O
5	producer	O

0	William	B-PER
1	O'Connor	I-PER
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	First	O
5	round	O
6	)	O

0	Albert	B-PER
1	Pujols	I-PER
2	[2]	O
3	(	O
4	2006	O
5	,	O
6	2010	O
7	)	O

0	Mark	B-PER
1	Jones	I-PER
2	:	O
3	(	O
4	1991-1999	O
5	,	O
6	2006	O
7	)	O

0	Lugdunum	B-LOC
1	(	O
2	modern	O
3	Lyon	B-LOC
4	)	O

0	Pioneer	B-ORG
1	Square	I-ORG
2	,	I-ORG
3	Seattle	I-ORG

0	Joe	B-PER
1	Shirley	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	Jr	I-PER
4	.	I-PER

0	The	O
1	family	O
2	eventually	O
3	settled	O
4	in	O
5	Egypt	B-ORG
6	in	O
7	February	O
8	1944	O
9	.	O

0	''	O
1	Pumped	B-ORG
2	Up	I-ORG
3	Kicks	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	–	O
6	Foster	B-ORG
7	the	I-ORG
8	People	I-ORG

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Tanzania	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O
5	-	O
6	Jakaya	B-PER
7	Kikwete	I-PER
8	(	O
9	1995-2006	O
10	)	O

0	Brian	B-ORG
1	Dillons	I-ORG
2	GAA	I-ORG

0	Ridley	B-PER
1	Scott	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Hans	B-PER
4	Zimmer	I-PER

0	Slavko	B-PER
1	Marić	I-PER
2	–	O
3	Hajduk	B-ORG
4	Beograd	I-ORG
5	(	O
6	2001–2006	O
7	)	O
8	,	O
9	Mladost	B-ORG
10	Lučani	I-ORG
11	(	O
12	2006–2008	O
13	)	O
14	,	O
15	Borac	B-ORG
16	Čačak	I-ORG
17	(	O
18	2008–2011	O
19	)	O
20	,	O
21	Sloboda	B-ORG
22	Užice	I-ORG
23	(	O
24	2011–2012	O
25	)	O
26	,	O
27	Radnički	B-ORG
28	Kragujevac	I-ORG
29	(	O
30	2012-2014	O
31	)	O
32	,	O
33	'	O
34	''	O
35	FK	B-ORG
36	Jagodina	I-ORG
37	''	O
38	'	O
39	(	O
40	2015–present	O
41	)	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	described	O
3	by	O
4	Breuning	B-PER
5	in	O
6	1982	O
7	.	O

0	Shipley	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	West	I-LOC
3	Yorkshire	I-LOC

0	Jefferson	B-PER
1	Davis	I-PER
2	!	O
3	!	O
4	2	O
5	!	O
6	!	O

0	They	O
1	wed	O
2	on	O
3	28	O
4	April	O
5	2007	O
6	in	O
7	their	O
8	Malibu	B-LOC
9	home	O
10	.	O

0	Native	B-LOC
1	North	I-LOC
2	American	I-LOC
3	Child	I-LOC
4	:	I-LOC
5	An	I-LOC
6	Odyssey	I-LOC
7	''	O

0	Redlich–Kwong	B-ORG
1	equation	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	state	I-ORG

0	Yu	B-PER
1	Darvish	I-PER
2	(	O
3	TEX	B-ORG
4	)	O
5	:	O

0	''	O
1	Samurai	B-ORG
2	7	I-ORG
3	''	O

0	Dev	B-PER
1	(	I-PER
2	actor	I-PER
3	)	I-PER

0	Party	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Action	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	POA	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	Princess	B-PER
1	Adélaïde	I-PER
2	of	I-PER
3	Orléans	I-PER

0	Children	B-ORG
1	's	I-ORG
2	Day	I-ORG
3	Festival	I-ORG

0	Hedley	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Texas	I-LOC

0	Final	B-ORG
1	Fantasy	I-ORG
2	concerts	I-ORG

0	Quta	B-LOC
1	Qutani	I-LOC
2	(	I-LOC
3	Bolivia	I-LOC
4	)	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	20px	O
3	99	B-ORG
4	Villeray	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	A	B-ORG
1	Few	I-ORG
2	Days	I-ORG
3	with	I-ORG
4	Me	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Crick	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Northamptonshire	I-LOC

0	List	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	Serbian	I-PER
3	monarchs	I-PER

0	R.	B-PER
1	Kelly	I-PER
2	–	O
3	``	O
4	Satisfy	B-ORG
5	You	I-ORG
6	''	O

0	Turkish	B-ORG
1	films	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	2010	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Nemapogon	B-LOC
2	ruricolella	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Stainton	O
6	,	O
7	1859	O
8	)	O

0	Latter	B-ORG
1	Day	I-ORG
2	Church	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Christ	I-ORG

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	DLCX	O
3	''	O
4	'	O
5	-	O
6	Waste	B-ORG
7	Management	I-ORG
8	,	I-ORG
9	Inc	I-ORG
10	.	I-ORG

0	the	O
1	``	O
2	Twelve	B-ORG
3	Steps	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	at	O
6	the	O
7	beginning	O
8	of	O
9	Chapter	O
10	5	O
11	``	O
12	How	O
13	It	O
14	Works	O
15	''	O

0	Boundary	B-LOC
1	Ranges	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	just	O
4	S	O
5	of	O
6	Iskut	B-LOC
7	River	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Volumes	B-ORG
2	3	I-ORG
3	&	I-ORG
4	4	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	(	O
7	1998	O
8	)	O

0	Cauchy	B-ORG
1	's	I-ORG
2	theorem	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	geometry	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	Eaton	B-ORG
1	High	I-ORG
2	School	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	grades	O
5	9-12	O
6	)	O

0	Prince	B-PER
1	Michael	I-PER
2	of	I-PER
3	Prussia	I-PER
4	(	O
5	1940–2014	O
6	)	O

0	Anastasia	B-PER
1	Martiusheva	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Alexei	B-PER
4	Rogonov	I-PER

0	C.D.	B-ORG
1	Atlético	I-ORG
2	Junior	I-ORG

0	Stick	B-ORG
1	(	I-ORG
2	unit	I-ORG
3	)	I-ORG

0	Bridgwater	B-ORG
1	Town	I-ORG
2	,	O
3	promoted	O
4	as	O
5	runners-up	O
6	in	O
7	Western	B-LOC
8	League	I-LOC

0	''Crockett	O
1	''	O
2	was	O
3	laid	O
4	down	O
5	by	O
6	the	O
7	Tacoma	B-ORG
8	Boatbuilding	I-ORG
9	Company	I-ORG
10	,	O
11	Tacoma	B-LOC
12	,	I-LOC
13	Washington	I-LOC
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	commissioned	O
17	24	O
18	June	O
19	1967	O
20	.	O

0	Morrisania	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Bronx	I-LOC

0	Governorate	B-LOC
1	General	I-LOC
2	of	I-LOC
3	Brazil	I-LOC
4	(	O
5	1549-1572	O
6	/	O
7	1578-1607	O
8	/	O
9	1613-1621	O
10	)	O

0	Football	B-ORG
1	League	I-ORG
2	Two	I-ORG
3	third-place	O
4	promotion	O
5	:	O
6	2005–06	B-ORG

0	International	B-ORG
1	Swimming	I-ORG
2	Federation	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	FINA	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	Ethnic	B-PER
1	stereotypes	I-PER
2	in	I-PER
3	comics	I-PER

0	Chestnut-capped	B-LOC
1	brush	I-LOC
2	finch	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Spain	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	09:00	O
1	PM	O
2	(	O
3	VIA	O
4	:	O
5	Alagankulam	B-LOC
6	)	O

0	Air	B-ORG
1	Command	I-ORG
2	and	I-ORG
3	Staff	I-ORG
4	College	I-ORG
5	,	O
6	Seminar	O
7	Program	O

0	''	O
1	Eilema	B-ORG
2	depressa	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Esper	O
6	,	O
7	1787	O
8	)	O

0	North	B-ORG
1	Carolina	I-ORG
2	General	I-ORG
3	Assembly	I-ORG
4	of	I-ORG
5	2003–04	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Robopit	B-ORG
2	''	O
3	-	O
4	Kokopeli	B-ORG
5	Digital	I-ORG
6	Studios	I-ORG
7	/	O
8	Altron	B-ORG

0	Dominic	B-PER
1	Mafham	I-PER
2	as	O
3	Robin	B-PER
4	Douglas-Home	I-PER

0	She	O
1	was	O
2	purposely	O
3	sunk	O
4	near	O
5	Les	B-LOC
6	Bergeronnes	I-LOC
7	,	I-LOC
8	Quebec	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	November	O
11	1960	O
12	.	O

0	Vasil	B-ORG
1	Levski	I-ORG
2	National	I-ORG
3	Military	I-ORG
4	University	I-ORG
5	,	O
6	Veliko	B-LOC
7	Tarnovo	I-LOC

0	Smokey	B-PER
1	Robinson	I-PER
2	handled	O
3	much	O
4	of	O
5	the	O
6	production	O
7	.	O

0	Member	O
1	of	O
2	Finnish	B-ORG
3	Academy	I-ORG
4	of	I-ORG
5	Sciences	I-ORG
6	,	O
7	2002–	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Jackson	I-PER
2	–	O
3	``	O
4	Earth	B-ORG
5	Song	I-ORG
6	''	O

0	National	B-ORG
1	Union	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	Students	I-ORG
4	(	I-ORG
5	Canada	I-ORG
6	)	I-ORG
7	(	O
8	disbanded	O
9	)	O

0	Patti	B-PER
1	McLeod276	I-PER
2	(	O
3	37.8	O
4	%	O
5	)	O

0	The	O
1	resulting	O
2	album	O
3	,	O
4	Last	B-ORG
5	Fair	I-ORG
6	Deal	I-ORG
7	Gone	I-ORG
8	Down	I-ORG
9	''	O
10	was	O
11	released	O
12	in	O
13	May	O
14	2001	O
15	.	O

0	43	O
1	-	O
2	Nutpimon	B-PER
3	Natthayalak	I-PER
4	,	O
5	(	O
6	Krabi	B-LOC
7	)	O

0	''	O
1	Papilio	B-LOC
2	alexanor	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	Esper	O
5	,	O
6	1800	O

0	Thief	B-LOC
1	River	I-LOC
2	Falls	I-LOC
3	,	I-LOC
4	Minnesota	I-LOC

0	Persona	B-ORG
1	2	I-ORG
2	:	I-ORG
3	Innocent	I-ORG
4	Sin	I-ORG

0	Rhododendron	B-LOC
1	subg.	I-LOC
2	Rhododendron	B-LOC

0	Aleksander	B-PER
1	Barkov	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	Jr	I-PER
4	.	I-PER

0	``	O
1	Express	B-ORG
2	Yourself	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	,	O
5	Madonna	B-PER
6	(	O
7	1989	O
8	)	O

0	Tony	B-PER
1	Parker	I-PER
2	(	O
3	24	O
4	)	O

0	Pierre	B-PER
1	Du	I-PER
2	Moulin	I-PER

0	Thalhimers	B-ORG
1	(	O
2	Richmond	B-LOC
3	)	O

0	Phil	B-PER
1	Gramm	I-PER
2	(	O
3	R-TX	O
4	)	O

0	John	B-PER
1	Isner	I-PER
2	7–6	O
3	(	O
4	4	O
5	)	O
6	,	O
7	5–7	O
8	(	O
9	5	O
10	)	O
11	,	O
12	7–5	O
13	,	O
14	6–4	O

0	''	O
1	Eupithecia	B-LOC
2	refertissima	I-LOC
3	''	O

0	He	O
1	is	O
2	part	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	Czech	B-ORG
6	Republic	I-ORG
7	men	I-ORG
8	's	I-ORG
9	national	I-ORG
10	volleyball	I-ORG
11	team	I-ORG
12	.	O

0	800BC	O
1	(	O
2	in	O
3	The	B-ORG
4	Odyssey	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	)	O

0	Dakaongo	B-LOC
1	(	O
2	1	O
3	245	O
4	inhabitants	O
5	)	O

0	Center	B-LOC
1	Township	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	Atchison	B-LOC
4	County	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Kansas	I-LOC

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Turkish	B-ORG
3	Super	I-ORG
4	Cup	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	''	O

0	Metadata	B-PER
1	Object	I-PER
2	Description	I-PER
3	Schema	I-PER

0	Events	O
1	from	O
2	the	O
3	year	O
4	'	O
5	''	O
6	1866	O
7	in	O
8	Scotland	B-LOC
9	''	O
10	'	O
11	.	O

0	It	O
1	lies	O
2	approximately	O
3	south-east	O
4	of	O
5	Sicienko	B-LOC
6	and	O
7	north-west	O
8	of	O
9	Bydgoszcz	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	Ted	B-PER
1	Freyer	I-PER
2	(	O
3	52	O
4	)	O

0	He	O
1	joined	O
2	Ayr	B-ORG
3	United	I-ORG
4	in	O
5	August	O
6	1999	O
7	,	O
8	and	O
9	remained	O
10	with	O
11	them	O
12	until	O
13	August	O
14	2000	O
15	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Perth	B-ORG
3	Thunder	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Maria	B-ORG
1	Adams	I-ORG
2	(	I-ORG
3	disambiguation	I-ORG
4	)	I-ORG

0	Johann	B-PER
1	Ludwig	I-PER
2	Krebs	I-PER

0	Constantine	B-PER
1	Dragaš	I-PER
2	(	O
3	Dragaš	B-LOC
4	)	O

0	Ami	B-PER
1	Koshimizu	I-PER
2	and	O
3	Mamiko	B-PER
4	Noto	I-PER

0	Gérald	B-PER
1	V	I-PER
2	d'Armagnac	I-PER

0	Banyan	B-PER
1	(	I-PER
2	clothing	I-PER
3	)	I-PER

0	He	O
1	migrated	O
2	to	O
3	Mexico	B-LOC
4	City	I-LOC
5	in	O
6	1986	O
7	.	O

0	Basilica	B-ORG
1	della	I-ORG
2	Santa	I-ORG
3	Casa	I-ORG

0	Full	B-ORG
1	Circle	I-ORG
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	2004	O
5	)	O

0	''	O
1	Col	B-LOC
2	des	I-LOC
3	Ares	I-LOC
4	''	O

0	Barry	B-ORG
1	Mackay	I-ORG
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	Quarterfinalist	O
5	)	O
6	''	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Bolton	I-PER
2	covered	O
3	the	O
4	song	O
5	on	O
6	his	O
7	1992	O
8	album	O
9	Timeless	B-LOC
10	:	I-LOC
11	The	I-LOC
12	Classics	I-LOC
13	''	O
14	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Andersen	I-PER
2	,	O
3	journalist	O
4	and	O
5	author	O

0	Till	O
1	2014	O
2	,	O
3	the	O
4	NMMC	O
5	was	O
6	headquartered	O
7	in	O
8	an	O
9	eight	O
10	storied	O
11	building	O
12	in	O
13	CBD	B-LOC
14	Belapur	I-LOC
15	.	O

0	Represented	O
1	Indigenous	B-ORG
2	All-Stars	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	2009	O
5	)	O

0	Southend	B-ORG
1	United	I-ORG
2	F.C	I-ORG
3	.	I-ORG

0	Episodes	B-ORG
1	''	O
2	,	O
3	2011	O
4	(	O
5	writer	O
6	/	O
7	producer	O
8	)	O

0	1992	B-ORG
1	Major	I-ORG
2	League	I-ORG
3	Baseball	I-ORG
4	expansion	I-ORG
5	draft	I-ORG

0	Crystal	B-PER
1	Snow	I-PER
2	Jenne	I-PER

0	Siliștea	B-LOC
1	River	I-LOC
2	(	I-LOC
3	Țibrin	I-LOC
4	)	I-LOC

0	Happy]]	O
1	''	O
2	–	O
3	Pharrell	B-PER
4	Williams	I-PER

0	Premier	B-PER
1	(	I-PER
2	Canada	I-PER
3	)	I-PER

0	Vinod	B-PER
1	Khanna	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Shabana	B-PER
4	Azmi	I-PER

0	Benjamin	B-PER
1	N.	I-PER
2	Cardozo	I-PER

0	Herbie	B-PER
1	Hancock	I-PER
2	(	O
3	born	O
4	1940	O
5	)	O

0	Communes	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	the	I-LOC
3	Aude	I-LOC
4	department	I-LOC

0	Jonathan	B-PER
1	Thomas	I-PER
2	,	O
3	3	O
4	.	O

0	Cark	B-ORG
1	and	I-ORG
2	Cartmel	I-ORG
3	railway	I-ORG
4	station	I-ORG

0	*Written	O
1	by	O
2	Val	B-PER
3	Guest	I-PER
4	and	O
5	Leslie	B-PER
6	Thomas	I-PER

0	Anurag	B-PER
1	Singh	I-PER
2	,	O
3	2012	O
4	/	O
5	13-2014	O
6	/	O
7	15	O

0	National	B-ORG
1	Coalition	I-ORG
2	Party	I-ORG
3	13.5	O
4	%	O

0	Beauvoir	B-PER
1	De	I-PER
2	Lisle	I-PER
3	,	O
4	1st	B-ORG
5	Dragoons	I-ORG
6	,	O
7	commanded	O
8	both	O
9	the	O
10	XIII	B-ORG
11	and	O
12	XV	B-ORG
13	Corps	I-ORG
14	.	O

0	Eastwood	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Houston	I-LOC

0	Jacqueline	B-PER
1	Novogratz	I-PER
2	is	O
3	the	O
4	founder	O
5	and	O
6	CEO	O
7	of	O
8	Acumen	O
9	.	O

0	``	B-ORG
1	Sign	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	the	I-ORG
4	Times	I-ORG
5	''	I-ORG
6	(	I-ORG
7	Bryan	I-ORG
8	Ferry	I-ORG
9	song	I-ORG
10	)	I-ORG
11	,	O
12	1978	O

0	Szczecin	B-LOC
1	–	O
2	95.7	O
3	MHz	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	found	O
3	in	O
4	Ecuador	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	Billy	B-PER
1	Vessels	I-PER
2	(	O
3	RB	O
4	)	O
5	:	O

0	Houston	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Tennessee	I-LOC

0	Lake	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	Banyoles	I-LOC
3	and	O
4	S'Agaró	B-ORG

0	Bugs	B-PER
1	Bunny	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Yosemite	B-PER
4	Sam	I-PER

0	Buxton	B-ORG
1	&	I-ORG
2	Leek	I-ORG
3	College	I-ORG

0	**	O
1	Maués	B-LOC
2	marmoset	I-LOC
3	,	O
4	''Mico	O
5	mauesi	O
6	''	O

0	''	O
1	The	B-ORG
2	World	I-ORG
3	at	I-ORG
4	Large	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	–	O
7	4:32	O

0	*Assemblyman	O
1	Bob	B-PER
2	Andrzejczak	I-PER
3	(	O
4	D	O
5	)	O
6	,	O
7	and	O

0	Seidou	B-PER
1	Njimoluh	I-PER
2	Njoya	I-PER

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	headquartered	O
3	in	O
4	Raleigh	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	May	O
1	10	O
2	–	O
3	Shel	B-PER
4	Silverstein	I-PER
5	,	O
6	68	O
7	,	O
8	children	O
9	's	O
10	poet	O

0	:	O
1	PG	O
2	87a-87b	O
3	:	O
4	Procopius	B-PER
5	of	I-PER
6	Gaza	I-PER

0	State	B-ORG
1	Senate	I-ORG
2	District	I-ORG
3	39	I-ORG

0	Miyazaki	B-ORG
1	Athletic	I-ORG
2	Stadium	I-ORG

0	:	O
1	''	O
2	Atomic	B-ORG
3	Dog	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	by	O
6	George	B-PER
7	Clinton	I-PER

0	They	O
1	currently	O
2	reside	O
3	in	O
4	Lexington	B-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Massachusetts	I-LOC
7	.	O

0	1:46.7	O
1	–	O
2	Edward	B-PER
3	Burns	I-PER

0	C	B-ORG
1	&	I-ORG
2	D	I-ORG
3	Canal	I-ORG
4	Museum	I-ORG

0	``	O
1	Stupid	B-ORG
2	Shit	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	–	O
5	Girlicious	B-ORG

0	Communes	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	the	I-LOC
3	Doubs	I-LOC
4	department	I-LOC

0	Emerson	B-PER
1	Aparecido	I-PER
2	Vivas	I-PER
3	Vergílio	I-PER

0	South	B-LOC
1	Los	I-LOC
2	Angeles	I-LOC

0	Burmese–Siamese	B-ORG
1	War	I-ORG
2	(	I-ORG
3	1759–60	I-ORG
4	)	I-ORG

0	Dance4life	B-ORG
1	event	O
2	2006	O
3	.	O

0	''	O
1	'Megahertz	O
2	''	O
3	'	O
4	from	O
5	Mighty	B-ORG
6	Med	I-ORG
7	''	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	The	B-LOC
3	Green	I-LOC
4	Monkey	I-LOC
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	``	O
1	Elégie	O
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	Jules	B-PER
5	Massenet	I-PER
6	)	O

0	He	O
1	came	O
2	to	O
3	Rossland	B-LOC
4	,	I-LOC
5	British	I-LOC
6	Columbia	I-LOC
7	in	O
8	1898	O
9	.	O

0	All	O
1	degrees	O
2	(	O
3	whether	O
4	traditional	O
5	on-campus	O
6	,	O
7	or	O
8	distance	O
9	)	O
10	are	O
11	recognized	O
12	by	O
13	the	O
14	New	B-ORG
15	England	I-ORG
16	Association	I-ORG
17	of	I-ORG
18	Schools	I-ORG
19	and	I-ORG
20	Colleges	I-ORG
21	and	O
22	the	O
23	State	B-ORG
24	of	I-ORG
25	Connecticut	I-ORG
26	;	O
27	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Ifni	B-LOC
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	Oslo	B-LOC
1	–	O
2	Ullevaal	B-ORG
3	Stadion	I-ORG
4	(	O
5	25,572	O
6	)	O

0	Tommy	B-PER
1	Aaron	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Sam	B-PER
3	Lowes	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	The	O
1	Malwa	B-LOC
2	Subah	I-LOC
3	existed	O
4	from	O
5	1568	O
6	to	O
7	1743	O
8	.	O

0	San	B-LOC
1	Cristóbal	I-LOC
2	de	I-LOC
3	La	I-LOC
4	Laguna	I-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	España	I-LOC

0	University	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Massachusetts	I-ORG
3	Boston	I-ORG

0	The	O
1	song	O
2	contains	O
3	samples	O
4	from	O
5	``	O
6	Try	B-ORG
7	Again	I-ORG
8	''	O
9	by	O
10	Aaliyah	B-PER
11	,	O
12	``	O
13	Breathe	B-ORG
14	and	I-ORG
15	Stop	I-ORG
16	''	O
17	by	O
18	Q-Tip	B-PER
19	,	O
20	and	O
21	``	O
22	N.T	O
23	.	O

0	Holy	B-ORG
1	Trinity	I-ORG
2	Church	I-ORG
3	,	I-ORG
4	Blythburgh	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Pick-Up	B-ORG
2	''	O
3	(	O
4	1933	O
5	)	O
6	with	O
7	Sylvia	B-PER
8	Sidney	I-PER

0	:	O
1	Hans	B-PER
2	N.	I-PER
3	Andersen	I-PER
4	(	O
5	11	O
6	)	O

0	Kevin	B-PER
1	Johnson	I-PER
2	(	O
3	9	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Riccardo	B-PER
3	Patrese	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	The	O
1	founder	O
2	Mustafa	B-PER
3	Kemal	I-PER
4	Atatürk	I-PER
5	died	O
6	.	O

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	TV-host	O
3	for	O
4	Parlamentet	B-ORG
5	in	O
6	2011	O
7	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	James	B-PER
3	Auckland	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	'	O
7	''	O
8	Travis	B-PER
9	Rettenmaier	I-PER
10	''	O
11	'7–5	O
12	,	O
13	6–7	O
14	(	O
15	6	O
16	)	O
17	,	O
18	[10–4]	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	7th	B-ORG
3	US	I-ORG
4	Army	I-ORG
5	HQ	I-ORG
6	,	O
7	Heidelberg	B-LOC
8	''	O
9	'	O
10	,	O
11	FRG	O

0	He	O
1	was	O
2	born	O
3	in	O
4	Upton	B-LOC
5	,	I-LOC
6	Massachusetts	I-LOC
7	and	O
8	died	O
9	in	O
10	Worcester	B-LOC
11	,	I-LOC
12	Massachusetts	I-LOC
13	.	O

0	Jesús	B-PER
1	Rubio	I-PER
2	Martín	I-PER

0	Amanda	B-PER
1	Magarian	I-PER
2	/	O
3	Jered	B-PER
4	Guzman	I-PER

0	He	O
1	is	O
2	buried	O
3	in	O
4	Père	B-LOC
5	Lachaise	I-LOC
6	Cemetery	I-LOC
7	.	O

0	Sivaji	B-PER
1	Ganesan	I-PER
2	,	O
3	Sripriya	B-PER
4	,	O
5	V.K.	B-ORG
6	Ramasamy	I-ORG

0	Both	O
1	his	O
2	parents	O
3	were	O
4	members	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	Plymouth	B-PER
8	Brethren	I-PER
9	.	O

0	Bourke-White	B-PER
1	,	I-PER
2	Margaret	I-PER
3	.	O

0	Marquis	B-PER
1	de	I-PER
2	Condorcet	I-PER

0	*12	O
1	August	O
2	1681	O
3	:	O
4	Charles	B-PER
5	Bertie	I-PER

0	Chita	B-PER
1	Rivera	I-PER
2	played	O
3	the	O
4	role	O
5	of	O
6	``	O
7	The	O
8	Leader	O
9	''	O
10	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Cate	B-PER
3	Blanchett	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Free	B-ORG
1	Software	I-ORG
2	Foundation	I-ORG
3	Europe	I-ORG

0	Way	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	the	I-ORG
3	Blade	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	(	O
6	2006	O
7	)	O

0	**Monarch	O
1	–	O
2	Emperor	B-PER
3	Go-Daigo	I-PER
4	(	O
5	1318–1339	O
6	)	O

0	Bhagwan	B-LOC
1	Mahaveer	I-LOC
2	Sanctuary	I-LOC
3	and	I-LOC
4	Mollem	I-LOC
5	National	I-LOC
6	Park	I-LOC

0	NBA	B-ORG
1	Rookie	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	the	I-ORG
4	Year	I-ORG
5	:	O
6	2007	O

0	A	O
1	modern	O
2	Twist	B-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	ride	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG
6	.	O

0	1–1	O
1	Rodrigo	B-PER
2	Taddei	I-PER
3	(	O
4	54	O
5	)	O

0	Double	B-LOC
1	Bayou	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Texas	I-LOC

0	The	O
1	album	O
2	was	O
3	a	O
4	commercial	O
5	success	O
6	and	O
7	sold	O
8	almost	O
9	eight	O
10	million	O
11	copies	O
12	,	O
13	according	O
14	to	O
15	Billboard	B-ORG
16	''	O
17	.	O

0	Jaipur	B-LOC
1	(	O
2	Palace	B-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	the	I-ORG
5	Winds	I-ORG
6	)	O

0	Norte	B-LOC
1	Region	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Portugal	I-LOC

0	US	B-ORG
1	Amateur	I-ORG
2	–	O
3	Bobby	B-PER
4	Jones	I-PER

0	Port	B-LOC
1	of	I-LOC
2	Spain	I-LOC
3	,	O
4	Trinidad	B-ORG
5	and	I-ORG
6	Tobago	I-ORG

0	(	O
1	82.07	O
2	)	O
3	'	O
4	''	O
5	Colin	B-PER
6	Osborne	I-PER
7	''	O
8	'	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Women	B-ORG
3	's	I-ORG
4	10,000	I-ORG
5	metres	I-ORG
6	''	O
7	'	O

0	New	B-ORG
1	Forest	I-ORG
2	Wildlife	I-ORG
3	Park	I-ORG
4	-	O
5	Hampshire	B-LOC

0	—	O
1	Arranging	O
2	lessons	O
3	from	O
4	Willie	B-PER
5	Maiden	I-PER

0	Henry	B-PER
1	I	I-PER
2	of	I-PER
3	Werle	I-PER

0	Venice	B-LOC
1	Canal	I-LOC
2	Historic	I-LOC
3	District	I-LOC

0	Richard	B-PER
1	Hanson	I-PER
2	Weightman	I-PER

0	All	O
1	tracks	O
2	written	O
3	by	O
4	Ray	B-PER
5	Davies	I-PER

0	``	O
1	California	B-ORG
2	Gurls	I-ORG
3	''	O
4	-	O
5	Katy	B-PER
6	Perry	I-PER

0	Brian	B-PER
1	O'Driscoll	I-PER
2	(	O
3	capt	O
4	.	O

0	Victory	O
1	shared	O
2	with	O
3	Eugen	B-PER
4	Bönsch	I-PER

0	19	O
1	,	O
2	,	O
3	Stockholm	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	Cirkus	B-ORG

0	Waverly	B-ORG
1	School	I-ORG
2	District	I-ORG
3	(	I-ORG
4	disambiguation	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	found	O
3	in	O
4	Europe	B-LOC
5	.	O

0	Lone	B-LOC
1	Tree	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Iowa	I-LOC

0	''	O
1	Metanarsia	B-LOC
2	guberlica	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	Nupponen	O
5	,	O
6	2010	O

0	Dwyane	B-PER
1	Wade	I-PER
2	(	O
3	39	O
4	)	O

0	2004	O
1	:	O
2	Real	B-ORG
3	Gone	I-ORG
4	Tour	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Replaced	O
1	by	O
2	Robbie	B-PER
3	Groff	I-PER
4	.	O

0	Interstate	B-ORG
1	88	I-ORG
2	(	I-ORG
3	Illinois	I-ORG
4	)	I-ORG

0	Isle	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Man	I-ORG
3	Railway	I-ORG
4	stations	I-ORG

0	632	O
1	,	O
2	Air	B-ORG
3	Force	I-ORG
4	Office	I-ORG
5	of	I-ORG
6	Special	I-ORG
7	Investigations	I-ORG

0	``	O
1	Gin	B-ORG
2	and	I-ORG
3	Juice	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	There	O
1	is	O
2	some	O
3	intimation	O
4	that	O
5	Father	O
6	Set	O
7	may	O
8	be	O
9	one	O
10	of	O
11	the	O
12	Great	B-ORG
13	Old	I-ORG
14	Ones	I-ORG
15	that	O
16	H.	B-PER
17	P.	I-PER
18	Lovecraft	I-PER
19	created	O
20	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Dušan	B-PER
3	Lajović	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	7–6	O
7	(	O
8	7–5	O
9	)	O
10	,	O
11	7–6	O
12	(	O
13	7–5	O
14	)	O

0	Vandré	B-PER
1	Sagrilo	I-PER
2	Monteiro	I-PER

0	San	B-LOC
1	Cristóbal	I-LOC
2	de	I-LOC
3	La	I-LOC
4	Laguna	I-LOC

0	Siah	B-LOC
1	Piran-e	I-LOC
2	Kasmai	I-LOC

0	before	O
1	1870	O
2	and	O
3	the	O
4	Third	B-LOC
5	Republic	I-LOC
6	or	O

0	Owl	B-PER
1	Eyes	I-PER
2	–	O
3	``	O
4	Pumped	B-ORG
5	Up	I-ORG
6	Kicks	I-ORG
7	''	O
8	(	O
9	Foster	B-ORG
10	the	I-ORG
11	People	I-ORG
12	)	O

0	K	B-ORG
1	(	I-ORG
2	Eighth	I-ORG
3	Avenue	I-ORG
4	Local	I-ORG
5	)	I-ORG

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	WCAU-TV	B-ORG
3	''	O
4	'	O

0	List	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	B-52	I-ORG
3	Units	I-ORG
4	of	I-ORG
5	the	I-ORG
6	United	I-ORG
7	States	I-ORG
8	Air	I-ORG
9	Force	I-ORG

0	**	O
1	High	B-ORG
2	Explosive	I-ORG
3	(	O
4	HE	O
5	)	O

0	His	O
1	son	O
2	,	O
3	John	B-PER
4	V	I-PER
5	,	O
6	cosied	O
7	up	O
8	to	O
9	Guaimar	B-PER
10	IV	I-PER
11	of	I-PER
12	Salerno	I-PER
13	and	O
14	eventually	O
15	did	O
16	homage	O
17	to	O
18	him	O
19	.	O

0	(	O
1	**	O
2	Represents	O
3	NFL	B-ORG
4	Combine	I-ORG
5	)	O

0	Francisco	B-PER
1	Clavet	I-PER
2	Marcelo	B-PER
3	Ríos	I-PER
4	Takao	B-PER
5	Suzuki	I-PER
6	Sjeng	B-PER
7	Schalken	I-PER

0	Head	O
1	coach	O
2	:	O
3	Todor	B-PER
4	Veselinović	I-PER

0	Council	B-ORG
1	of	I-ORG
2	Churches	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Malaysia	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	The	B-ORG
2	Partridge	I-ORG
3	Family	I-ORG
4	''	O

0	File	O
1	:	O
2	J150W-Ayers.jpg	O
3	|Sir	O
4	Henry	B-PER
5	Ayers	I-PER

0	Pedro	B-PER
1	Téllez-Girón	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	1st	I-PER
4	Duke	I-PER
5	of	I-PER
6	Osuna	I-PER

0	BP	B-ORG
1	Ford	I-ORG
2	Abu	I-ORG
3	Dhabi	I-ORG
4	World	I-ORG
5	Rally	I-ORG
6	Team	I-ORG

0	Common	B-LOC
1	ringed	I-LOC
2	plover	I-LOC
3	,	O
4	''Charadrius	O
5	hiaticula	O
6	''	O

0	Villefranche	B-LOC
1	near	O
2	Nice	B-LOC
3	.	O

0	``	O
1	Love	B-ORG
2	Needs	I-ORG
3	No	I-ORG
4	Disguise	I-ORG
5	''	O

0	Mang	B-LOC
1	Thít	I-LOC
2	District	I-LOC

0	(	O
1	See	O
2	article	O
3	:	O
4	Entropy	B-ORG
5	(	I-ORG
6	statistical	I-ORG
7	views	I-ORG
8	)	I-ORG
9	)	O
10	.	O

0	Lancelot	B-PER
1	Strong	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	the	I-PER
4	Shield	I-PER
5	''	O
6	1-2	O
7	(	O
8	1983	O
9	)	O

0	''Look	O
1	Out	O
2	,	O
3	Houndour	B-ORG
4	!	O

0	Midnight	B-ORG
1	at	I-ORG
2	Minton	I-ORG
3	's	I-ORG
4	''	O
5	(	O
6	1941	O
7	)	O

0	Legal	B-ORG
1	systems	I-ORG
2	of	I-ORG
3	the	I-ORG
4	world	I-ORG

0	This	O
1	was	O
2	the	O
3	first	O
4	production	O
5	that	O
6	Charlie	B-PER
7	Chaplin	I-PER
8	came	O
9	to	O
10	.	O

0	Milt	B-PER
1	Pappas	I-PER
2	,	O
3	2012	O

0	He	O
1	died	O
2	in	O
3	Romillé	B-LOC
4	.	O

0	The	O
1	ports	O
2	of	O
3	Cádiz	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	La	B-LOC
6	Spezia	I-LOC
7	,	O
8	Naples	B-LOC
9	and	O
10	Toulon	B-LOC
11	were	O
12	visited	O
13	.	O

0	Geneva	B-ORG
1	II	I-ORG
2	Conference	I-ORG
3	on	I-ORG
4	Syria	I-ORG

0	Stoke	B-ORG
1	Bridge	I-ORG
2	,	I-ORG
3	Ipswich	I-ORG

0	''	O
1	Teniorhinus	B-LOC
2	niger	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Druce	O
6	,	O
7	1910	O
8	)	O

0	Aloha	B-ORG
1	Bowl	I-ORG
2	:	O
3	22	O
4	Michigan	B-LOC
5	State	I-LOC
6	33	O
7	,	O
8	23	O
9	13	O

0	''	O
1	Scoparia	B-LOC
2	niphospora	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Meyrick	O
6	,	O
7	1884	O
8	)	O

0	*1973	O
1	''North	O
2	Face	O
3	''	O
4	,	O
5	Wetterhorn	B-LOC
6	Peak	I-LOC
7	,	O
8	San	B-LOC
9	Juan	I-LOC
10	Mountains	I-LOC
11	,	O
12	Colorado	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	''	O
1	Mythimna	B-LOC
2	impura	I-LOC
3	''	O
4	(	O
5	Hübner	O
6	,	O
7	1808	O
8	)	O

0	Nicolaus	B-PER
1	Olahus	I-PER
2	(	O
3	1543	O
4	-	O
5	1548	O
6	)	O

0	Roy	B-PER
1	Stewart	I-PER
2	as	O
3	Nosha	O
4	(	O
5	uncredited	O
6	)	O

0	Palau	B-ORG
1	Municipal	I-ORG
2	d'Esports	I-ORG
3	de	I-ORG
4	Badalona	I-ORG

0	Glenwood	B-LOC
1	(	O
2	vast	O
3	majority	O
4	)	O

0	Imperial	B-ORG
1	College	I-ORG
2	Business	I-ORG
3	School	I-ORG

0	53	O
1	feet	O
2	(	O
3	16	O
4	m	O
5	)	O
6	-	O
7	Squaw	B-ORG
8	Island	I-ORG
9	Light	I-ORG
10	,	O
11	Michigan	B-LOC

0	José	B-PER
1	Luís	I-PER
2	Ábalos	I-PER
3	Meco	I-PER

0	U.S.	B-ORG
1	Route	I-ORG
2	211	I-ORG

0	She	O
1	was	O
2	reportedly	O
3	set	O
4	against	O
5	moving	O
6	from	O
7	St	B-LOC
8	Albans	I-LOC
9	,	O
10	Hertfordshire	B-LOC
11	to	O
12	York	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	North	B-LOC
15	Yorkshire	I-LOC
16	,	O
17	resulting	O
18	in	O
19	her	O
20	husband	O
21	turning	O
22	down	O
23	the	O
24	offer	O
25	.	O

0	List	B-PER
1	of	I-PER
2	works	I-PER
3	by	I-PER
4	Auguste	I-PER
5	Carli	I-PER

0	In	O
1	September	O
2	2011	O
3	,	O
4	he	O
5	signed	O
6	a	O
7	one-year	O
8	contract	O
9	with	O
10	PAOK	B-ORG
11	in	O
12	Greece	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	Six	B-ORG
1	Celan	I-ORG
2	Songs	I-ORG
3	•	I-ORG
4	The	I-ORG
5	Ballad	I-ORG
6	of	I-ORG
7	Kastriot	I-ORG
8	Rexhepi	I-ORG

0	1968–69	B-LOC
1	Honduran	I-LOC
2	Liga	I-LOC
3	Nacional	I-LOC

0	Drums	B-ORG
1	and	I-ORG
2	Guns	I-ORG

0	Pat	B-PER
1	Garrity	I-PER
2	,	O
3	George	B-PER
4	McCloud	I-PER
5	(	O
6	15	O
7	)	O

0	He	O
1	started	O
2	by	O
3	beating	O
4	Iván	B-PER
5	Navarro	I-PER
6	in	O
7	straight	O
8	sets	O
9	and	O
10	eventually	O
11	lost	O
12	to	O
13	12th	O
14	ranked	O
15	David	B-PER
16	Ferrer	I-PER
17	.	O

0	Aspropotamos	B-LOC
1	,	I-LOC
2	Trikala	I-LOC

0	In	O
1	1606	O
2	and	O
3	1607	O
4	the	O
5	Plymouth	B-ORG
6	Company	I-ORG
7	sent	O
8	ships	O
9	into	O
10	the	O
11	area	O
12	to	O
13	colonize	O
14	,	O
15	but	O
16	the	O
17	settlers	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	Popham	B-LOC
21	Colony	I-LOC
22	and	O
23	those	O
24	who	O
25	settled	O
26	along	O
27	the	O
28	Kennebec	B-LOC
29	River	I-LOC
30	returned	O
31	to	O
32	England	B-LOC
33	in	O
34	1608	O
35	.	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	King	B-LOC
3	Edward	I-LOC
4	Point	I-LOC
5	''	O
6	'	O

0	The	B-PER
1	Power	I-PER
2	Team	I-PER
3	(	I-PER
4	TV	I-PER
5	series	I-PER
6	)	I-PER

0	Barbara	B-PER
1	Schett	I-PER
2	Amanda	B-PER
3	Coetzer	I-PER
4	Jana	B-PER
5	Novotná	I-PER
6	Lindsay	B-PER
7	Davenport	I-PER

0	Bad	B-LOC
1	Schwartau	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	Schleswig-Holstein	B-LOC

0	**	O
1	''	O
2	Kingdom	B-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Pamplona	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	'	O
7	-	O
8	García	B-PER
9	Sánchez	I-PER
10	II	I-PER
11	(	O
12	994–1004	O
13	)	O

0	Dwight	B-PER
1	Howard	I-PER
2	(	O
3	12	O
4	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Chris	B-PER
3	Short	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O
6	(	O
7	6–7	O
8	)	O

0	'	O
1	''	O
2	Olli	B-PER
3	Tuominen	I-PER
4	''	O
5	'	O

0	Lalit	B-PER
1	Mohan	I-PER
2	Sharma	I-PER
3	,	O
4	former	O
5	Chief	B-PER
6	Justice	I-PER
7	of	I-PER
8	India	I-PER

0	A	B-ORG
1	Dramatic	I-ORG
2	Turn	I-ORG
3	of	I-ORG
4	Events	I-ORG
5	''	O
6	(	O
7	2011	O
8	)	O

0	''Lawe	O
1	''	O
2	left	O
3	the	O
4	Gulf	B-LOC
5	of	I-LOC
6	Tonkin	I-LOC
7	on	O
8	14	O
9	May	O
10	.	O

0	North	B-LOC
1	Frontenac	I-LOC
2	,	I-LOC
3	Ontario	I-LOC
